welcome to category five technology TV
カテゴリ5テクノロジーテレビへようこそ
this is episode number 547 and this week
これ はエピソード番号547であり、今週
we at well we're celebrating pi week
我々 はまあまあ我々はpiの週を祝っている
we'll call it but pi day was Wednesday
我々は それ を呼び出すつもり だが、パイの日は水曜日だった
and so we are celebrating by showing you
そして私達はあなたに見せることによって祝っています
some of the cool projects that you can
その こと ができ ます クールなプロジェクト のいくつか
do with a Raspberry Pi we've also got a
我々はまた持っているラズベリーパイでやる
huge announcement from the Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイからの大きな発表
foundation want to stick around if
基礎があれば固執したい
you're a PI fan or if you're just
あなただけなら 、あなたはPIファンですか
thinking okay maybe maybe I want to buy
多分 、多分私が購入したい 大丈夫思考
a Raspberry Pi stick around we've got
ラズベリーパイは、私たちが持っている固執します
some news for him this is category 5
彼のためにいくつかのニュースこれはカテゴリ5です
technology TV
テクノロジーテレビ
[Music]
[音楽]
[Applause]
[拍手]
our live recordings are trusted only to
私たちのライブ録音だけ に 、信頼されています
solid-state drives by Kingston
キングストンによるソリッドステートドライブ
technology revive your computer with
技術はあなたのコンピュータを復活させます
improved performance and reliability
性能と信頼性の向上
over traditional hard drives with
従来のハードドライブに
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams with
Kingston SSDカテゴリー5のTVストリーム
Telestream Wirecast and nimble streamer
Telestream Wirecastと機敏なストリーマ
tune in every week on roku Kodi Plex and
roku Kodi Plex で毎週チューニングしている
other HLS video players for local show
ローカルショー用の他のHLSビデオプレーヤー
times visit category 5 TV category 5 TV
時間は、カテゴリ5テレビカテゴリ 5テレビをご覧ください。
is a member of the tech podcast network
Tech Podcastネットワークのメンバーです。
if it's tech gets here cat 5 dot TV
それがハイテクであればここに 猫5ドットテレビ
slash TPM and the international
TPMと国際を切り詰める
association of internet broadcasters cat
インターネット放送局協会猫
5 dot TV slash ia IB welcome to category
5 ドットテレビスラッシュIA IB カテゴリへようこそ
five technology TV I'm Jeff Weston I'm
five technology TV私は Jeff Westonです
Robbie
ロビー
nice to see you folks hope you're having
素敵なあなたを見るために人々は あなたが 持っ ている願っています
a great week lots of exciting things
エキサイティングな もの の偉大週間ロット
today oh it's very exciting indeed oh
今日は、 ああ、それは、 ああ 確かに非常にエキサイティングです
yeah I mean we know what's coming up but
ええ、 私たちは何 が起き ているのか知っ ていますが、
we're not telling you it's a surprise
私たちはあなたにそれが驚きだと言っているのではありません
it's true so how's your week my week has
それは本当だから あなたの今週の週 は どうですか
been amazing so far yeah have you
これまでのところ素晴らしかった
recovered from Friday night uh I I
ええと金曜日の夜から回収したI I
believe I have recovered from Friday
金曜日から回復したと思う
night truth be told I I've kind of
夜の真実は私が親切だ
caught the bug I found yes I find myself
私が見つけたバグをキャッチはい、私は自分自身を見つけます
sitting in front of discord waiting for
待っている不和の 前 に座っ
a rain dance who aren't aware completely
完全に意識していないレインダンス
separate from category five technology
カテゴリー 5技術とは別に
TV Jeff and I were here in the studio
TV Jeffと私はスタジオにいました
and we were participating in what was
私たちは参加 していた
called a turtle typhoon and what that is
カメ台風と呼ばれる
is turtle coin which we've shown on the
私達がに示したタートルコインです
show here a cryptocurrency that's on the
ここにある暗号通貨を表示する
up-and-up and we had a lot of fun I mean
アップとアップ と私たちは私が意味する多くの楽しみを持っていた
there was lost there was over was it
そこにはそれが あった上であった失われました
over a million turtle coins even more
さらに 100万以上のカメの硬貨
than that I think it got close to two
それよりも2つ 近くなっ たと 思う
million if I remember so that given away
万人離れて 与えられたように、私が覚えていれば
absolutely free to the participants in
の参加者 は 絶対に無料 です。
the in the discord so it was a lot of
それは多くのことでした
fun now again not not directly
直接ではない
associated with category five but if you
カテゴリ5に関連付けられていますが、
are interested in that I did post the
私が 投稿 したことに興味が あります
video on our YouTube channel so you can
YouTube チャンネルの ビデオ
go check that out if you want to learn
あなた が 学び たいのであれば、チェックしてください
more about cryptocurrency turtle coin in
暗号通貨タートルコインの詳細
particular we happen to cover a lot on
特に私たちはよくカバーしています
last week's episode yeah exactly so we
先週のエピソード うんまさに 私たち
talked about it from our perspective
私たちの観点からそれについて話しました
here at the studio but then to actually
ここはスタジオですが、 実際には
see it in action is what was happening
実際にそれが起こっているのを見てください
that's fun so long night it was a lot of
とても長い夜がとても楽しかったです
fun yes exciting news for you and you
あなたとあなたの ための楽しいはいエキサイティングなニュース
and me I love your wonderful sweater
私はあなたの素晴らしいセーターが大好きです
thank you
ありがとうございました
I basically photocopied the the wall and
私は基本的に壁をコピーして
stuck it on my chest now that's not the
それは私の胸に貼り付けました
exciting news the exciting nudist news
エキサイティングなニュースエキサイティングな ヌーディストのニュース
is that for a limited time we do have
限られた時間のために我々が持っているということです
some apparel
いくつかのアパレル
so check out cat5 TV slash shirts just
だからちょうどcat5 TVスラッシュシャツを チェックしてください
like that now it's a way that you can
そのように今それ はあなたができる 方法 です
support the shows that you love here at
あなたがここで好きな ショー をサポートする
category 5 at that at that website it's
そのWebサイトでそれで カテゴリ5
a teespring campaign and that basically
ティープリングキャンペーンとそれは基本的に
how that works is folks like you who
どのように動作する あなたのような人々 が 誰 です か
love the show and want to support us but
ショーを 愛し、 私たちをサポートしたいのですが
also want to Don awesome apparel you can
また、 あなたができる 素晴らしい衣服を 着用したいです
get on there and you can purchase a
そこに着くとあなたは 購入する ことができます
shirt a t-shirt or a sweatshirt and and
Tシャツやスウェットシャツを着て、そして
you'll be supporting category 5 TV
カテゴリー5のテレビをサポートします
you'll be supporting what we do here and
あなたは私たちがここでやっていることをサポートしてくれるでしょう
it's a limited time run it's a chance
限られた時間しか走れないそれはチャンスだ
for you to get some some merch which we
あなたが私達にある いくつかの商品 を手に入れるため に
don't always do like there's not the
がないように常にするわけではあり ません
wise yeah it has I can't believe our
賢明なそれは持っている
last shirt campaign with t spring 2014
T 春2014 との最後のシャツキャンペーン
it's big it's 2037 now as we brought so
私たちが 持ってきた ので 今は2037年です
you know if you if you wonder how
あなたがどうすればあなたが不思議に思うなら知っている
limited-edition is this stuff well you
限定版 は あなた もこのもの
could be looking for years in the future
将来の 年 を探している可能性があります
but yeah this shirt comes from there so
しかし、このシャツはあちらから来ている
I got this during the 2014 run you can
私はあなたができる2014年の実行中にこれを得ました
see it obviously has has continued yeah
それは明らかにそう続けてきたね
- like it hasn't faded it hasn't held up
- それが衰えていないように、それは我慢できませんでした
got all nasty and the sweaters I was
すべての意地の悪い、私がいたセーター
noticing on the teespring campaign the
ティープリングキャンペーンに注目する
the sweatshirts are relatively expensive
スウェットシャツは比較的 高価です
and I and I started looking around and I
そして私と私は 周り を 見 始め ました そして私は
realize that they're actually cheaper
彼らは実際に安いことを認識
than going into the stores our friend
私たちの友人の店 に 入る よりも
Heather really brown showed me some
本当に 茶色のヘザーが私にいくつか見せてくれた
local stores that are selling
販売している地元の店
sweatshirts and it's unbelievable how
スウェットとそれは信じられないほどの 方法です
much it costs to buy a sweatshirt while
スウェットシャツを買うの にかかる費用は
so but these ones are nice and thick and
それで、これらのものは素晴らしくて厚いです、そして
warm these are like campfire sweatshirt
暖かいこれらはキャンプファイヤーのスウェットシャツのようなものです
yes yeah
ええ
comfy cozy goodies I should wear the
私が着るべき快適な居心地の良いグッズ
hoodie all night long what I feel like
私は 長い ように感じるものを すべて夜パーカー
there's a wrap coming oh and that'd be
おおよそラップがあり ます。
if only I was prepared
私だけが用意されていたら
but head on over to cap five dot TV
しかし、 5ドットテレビをキャップするために向かいます
slash shirts and you can support that
シャツをスラッシュとあなたは それを サポートすることができます
campaign be a part of it
キャンペーンはその一部になる
and incidentally if you send us a
そして偶然に 私達に私達 を送れば
picture of yourself or a loved one or
自分自身や愛する人の またはの絵
whoever that you've purchased it for if
購入した人は誰でも
you send a picture of y'all wearing our
あなたは私たちを身に着けているのy'all の写真を送ります
t-shirts or whatever it is that you buy
Tシャツか それが あなたが買う ものであれ何でも
then we will post it on the show we will
それから私達は私達がするショー に それを投稿し ます
give you a shout out live on the air
空気でライブ あなたに 一言コメントを 配ります
you're 10 seconds of fame it's good
あなたは 名声の10秒 だ それは良いことです
times there you go
何度か行きます
good times alright so we've also been
いい時間に大丈夫な ので我々も行ってきた
giving away a copy of debt effect to VR
VR に 借金の 効果の コピー を配る
I've been doing that for a while we
私はしばらくそれをやっています
still have copies to hit to give out
まだあきらめるためにヒットするコピーを持っている
unbelievable I know good on them for
信じられない私は、 彼らのために 良い知っています
sending out all these free copies for
これらすべての無料コピーを
you oh they they hooked us up huge so
ああ、彼らは私たちを巨大につなげた
you don't want to miss out so check it
見逃したくないのでチェックしてください
out it's really really easy to do you
本当に 簡単です
load up your email whatever you use push
あなたがプッシュを使用するものは何でもあなたの電子メールをロードする
the email button that's right and then
その後、右の電子メールボタン
you want to send us an email with how
あなたは私たちに どうやっ てEメールを送りたいですか
you're watching category 5 what you
カテゴリ5を見ています
what's your system like are you watching
あなたのシステムはあなたが見ているもののようなものです
in a Roku are you doing on YouTube is
Rokuの 中で 、あなたは、YouTube上でやっているの です
your Kodi how do you watch this show
あなたのコディこの番組をどのように見ますか
maybe you're on TV and you're and you're
多分あなたはテレビに出ていてあなたはあなただ
watching us through your cable network
あなたの ケーブルネットワーク を通して私たちを見て
let us know and we'll put you in for
私たちが知っていると我々はのため にあなたを置きますよ
winning Dead Effect 2 VR I'm picturing a
Dead Effect 2 VR を受賞しました。
projector oh yeah pointed at the clouds
プロジェクターああええ 雲を 指して
with category 5 up on the clouds select
カテゴリー5で雲の上を 選択
about so maybe that's how you're
だから多分それはあなたがどのようにあなたがいるか
watching maybe that's how you're
多分それを見ている
watching I like that just category 5
私はそれだけでカテゴリ5が好き
right there in the clouds and every time
雲の中 やその都度
that's called we answer a tech question
技術的な質問に答えます
there you go yeah never sleep don't miss
あそこに行くねえ眠らない絶対にお 見逃しなく
out on that so it goes to contest at
その上でそれは でコンテスト に行きます
category 5 TV that's the email I just
カテゴリ5のテレビそれが私のメールです
you want to send it to nice and simple
あなたは素敵で シンプルに それを送りたいです
yeah we've got to take a really quick
ええ、 私たちは本当に速くしなければなりません
break it is well this week we're
今週は順調です
celebrating pi day yes we're gonna tell
pi dayを祝うはい私達は言うつもりだ
you what that's all about and we've got
あなたはそれがすべてについてのものであり、 私たちは持っています
some exciting news from the Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイからいくつかのエキサイティングな ニュース
foundation coming right out don't go
すぐに 出て くる財団 は行かない
anywhere
どこでも
[Music]
[音楽]
Jeff Weston Jemma you're building a
あなたが 構築 しているジェフ・ウェストン ジェマ
brand-new beautiful website what aren't
真新しい 美しいウェブサイトは何ではありません
you you're terrible actor what does
あなたはあなたがひどい俳優なのですか
where acting comes into play you're
演技の出番 あなたがしています
supposed to act okay are you building a
大丈夫 に行動することになってい ます
really cool website are you building a
本当にかっこいいウェブサイト
really cool website just because Jeff is
ジェフがそうであるという理由だけで本当にクールなウェブサイト
confused doesn't mean you have to be
混乱し ている からと いって そうで ある必要 はない
visit cap five dot TV slash DreamHost
キャップ5ドットテレビ スラッシュ DreamHostを訪問キャップ
to sign up for unlimited web hosting for
無制限の Webホスティングに申し込む
your website with unlimited email
あなたのウェブサイトは 無制限のEメールで
accounts MySQL databases the latest
MySQLデータベース の最新アカウント
version of PHP WordPress and more and
PHP WordPressのバージョン以上
even a free domain name registration
無料のドメイン 名登録でも
it's less than six dollars per month so
月に 6ドル以下なので
sign up today cat five TV slash dream
今日のサインアップ猫5 テレビスラッシュの 夢
host welcome back this is category five
ホストへようこそこれはカテゴリ5です
technology TV so glad to have you here
テクノロジーテレビはあなたをここに持っていてとても嬉しいです
joining us an exciting exciting episode
エキサイティングなエキサイティングなエピソードにご参加ください
it's a great week I love the Raspberry
ラズベリーが大好きです。
Pi no we do and I every year I look
Pi no私たちがやっていると私は毎年見て
forward to this week because it's got pi
それはパイを持っているので今週に 進む
day well what happens when pi day falls
パイの日が下がる日も 何が起こります
on a Wednesday we've got a feature it
水曜日に我々はそれを機能を持っています
now of course this week is the
今週はもちろん今
celebration of pi day which if you're
pi dayのお祝い
not familiar with that Wednesday was
その 水曜日には なじみが なかっ た
March 14th right which is 3.14 in the
3月14日右の3.14 は
geeky system yes so 3.14 it's like may
こっけいなシステムは いそう3.14それは5月のようです
the 4th be with you you know we've we've
第四は、 あなたが私たちがきました知っている あなたと一緒に
kind of thing as geekdom has claimed
オタクが主張しているようなこと
days for its own and 3.14 is one of
3.14はそれ自身のための日
those so this week we celebrate pi day
今週はパイデーを祝います
yes and if you don't know what pi is
はい 、あなた はパイが何であるか分からない ならば
it's a mathematical equation a delicious
それはおいしい数学式です
circle it's true but it is a number that
サークルそれは本当ですが、 それはその数字です
does not end it's a mathematical
数学的なもので はありません
equation that is and I was this song
それ は私がこの歌だった方程式
got stuck in my head Jeff thank you for
私の頭にはまったジェフありがとう
that oh yes good job
ああはい、 いい仕事
yes that's gonna be stuck in my head oh
はい、それはああ私の頭の 中で立ち往生するつもり だ
you are horrible what have you done all
あなたはすべてをやったことがひどいです
right
右
didn't you just say no we won for I was
私が勝ったからといって勝ったのではない
reading this week that pie is now up to
今週読んでいるパイは今
twenty two trillion characters long are
22兆文字の長さは
they still hashing this they're still
彼らはまだこれをハッシュしています
Hasek it out oh man twenty two trillion
ああ男22 兆兆
characters long and they say the hash
文字が長く、 彼らはハッシュを言う
power of the cryptocurrency Network get
cryptocurrency ネットワークのパワーGET
the blockchain working on figuring out
ブロックチェーンが考え出すことに取り組んで
pi and see when this crazy thing will
piとこのクレイジー なことが いつ行われるかを参照してください
ever end where do you even store that
どこにでもあなたはそれを保存するのですか
long of a number I have no clue but I
私は何の手がかりもありません
was who's reading it going if they ever
彼らが今まで読んでいるのは誰なのか
get to the end of pi the world is
世界は パイの終わりに到達する
probably gonna crash because people are
おそらく 人々がいる のでクラッシュするつもり です
gonna display it's gonna ruin everything
それはすべてを台無しにするつもりです
they know everything will just fail
彼らはすべてがただ失敗することを知っています
that's right
そうですよね
but Pi in the respect that we're
しかし、 パイ 、我々はしている点 で 、
discussing it tonight has to do with the
それについて議論する今夜はと関係があります
Raspberry Pi the microcomputer that fits
ラズベリーパイ フィットマイコン
in the palm of your hand and we've got
あなたの手のひらの上で私たちは持っています
an announcement for you this week being
今週のあなたへのお知らせ
pi day week we're gonna call it because
pi day week私達はそれを次の理由で呼ぶつもりです
we don't know when you're watching this
いつ これを見て いるのかわからない
whether it be this week or next or
今週か来週か
whatever but the week that we are
私たちがいる週以外は何でも
broadcasting is pi week mm-hmm there you
放送はパイ週間 mm-mm
go
行く
and the Raspberry Pi foundation has
そしてラズベリーパイ財団は
chosen this week to divulge the pi3
今週、 pi3を公開するために選ばれました
model b+ so could we say that this is
モデルb +だから、 これ は
going to be a PI three killer
PI 3キラーになる
I think we can safely say that now we
私たちは 今、私 たちは安全に言う こと ができると思います
finally have an undisputed pi three
誰もが認めるパイ3を持っています
killer well yeah that even the Raspberry
ラズベリーさえもキラーよく
Pi fan base cannot disagree with us
パイファン ベースは 私たちと同意 できない
can't hate on us and can't give us the
私たち を憎むことはできませんし、私たちに与えることもできません
thumbs down so hey you see that button
親指ダウンしてねえあなたはそのボタンが表示されます
down there give us a thumbs up that's
あそこに親指を立てる
how it goes so what makes it so special
どうやって行くのか
well first of all we've been waiting for
まさにまず私たちが待っていたのは
a more powerful Raspberry Pi yes
より強力なラズベリーパイ はい
microcomputer now 1.4 gigahertz 64-bit
マイクロコンピュータは現在 1.4ギガヘルツ64ビット
processor now at 1.4 it was previously
プロセッサは今1.4でそれは以前にあった
1.2 so what happens is it's gonna run at
1.2 だから何が起きるの か
1.4 gigahertz and then as it gets hot
1.4ギガヘルツ、そして暑くなるにつれて
it's going to downscale to 1.2 so okay
1.2に縮小するので、 問題ありません。
the throttled cpu is as fast as the
調整されたCPUは
fastest the CPU would ever be on a on a
最速のCPUが
previous generation Raspberry Pi 3 ok a
前世代のラズベリーパイ3
couple of other key points here with the
ここで他の重要なポイントのカップル
Raspberry Pi 3 model B plus 1 and this
ラズベリーパイ3モデルBプラス 1本これ
is probably I should save the best for
おそらく私はのために最善を保存する必要があります
last but I got it I gotta tell you
最後にしかし 私はそれを得た
Gigabit Ethernet finally we've got
ギガビットイーサネットがついに登場
Gigabit Ethernet it's like we have
ギガビットイーサネット
stepped into 1997 pocket-sized computers
1997年のポケットサイズのコンピュータにステップイン
with gigabit ethernet now all of a
ギガビットイーサネットで今のすべての
sudden we've been talking about things
突然私たちは 物事 について話してきました
like Plex PI which we're gonna bring up
私たちが育てるつもりだプレックスPIのような
tonight and streaming video over our
今夜のストリーミングビデオ
network and some people have said well
ネットワークと何人かの人々はよく言った
I've been trying to use Plex PI with the
私は Plex PIを
Wi-Fi and the Raspberry Pi why isn't it
Wi-Fi と ラズベリーPiは、なぜ そうではありません
working don't even go there ok because
働いても大丈夫ではありません
the Wi-Fi on these things traditionally
伝統的にこれらのことにWi-Fi
sucks yes and even if it was great Wi-Fi
はい、たとえそれが素晴らしいWi-Fiであっても吸います
the Wi-Fi just the standard itself is
Wi-Fi は規格そのものです
too slow for what you want Plex PI to be
Plex PIにするには遅すぎる
able to do that's right so you plug in
そうすることができるのであなたは差し込む
an Ethernet cable but the Raspberry Pi 3
イーサネットケーブルだがラズベリーパイ3
and previous generations we're only a
前の世代は私たちだけです
hundred megabits per second so now you
だから今 、毎秒百メガビット
throw a gigabit which is a thousand
千であるギガビットを投げる
megabits per second in there and you've
1秒あたりのメガビット
got a low speed well technically it's
それはだ技術的にも低速です
about three times the speed I don't know
知らない スピードの約3 倍
how that math happens I think because
どうやってその数学が起こるのか
you don't truly get a thousand megabits
あなたは本当に千メガビットを得ない
per second but so you're gonna get at
毎秒しかし、あなたがつもりで取得しています
least like three times the speed out of
少なくとも3倍のスピード
the Ethernet so when you plug in your
イーサネットは、そう、 あなたに接続すると
Plex PI server or whatever it is you're
Plex PI Serverまたはそれが あなたが 何であれ何でも
doing with your Raspberry Pi 3 the B+ is
あなたのラズベリーパイ3で やって いるB +は
going to give you much better
あなたをもっと良くするつもりです
performance that I'm excited about now
今 興奮しているパフォーマンス
they've also improved the Wi-Fi on it I
彼らはそれのWi-Fiも改善しました
didn't have they've gone to 5g 5 G so
5 G 5 Gになって いない ので
you're looking at much faster Wi-Fi I'm
もっと速いWi-Fiを見ているのですが
not sure how this is going to play out
これが出てプレーしようとして いる方法がわかりません
because with my Raspberry Pi 3 I
私の ラズベリーパイ3私 と一緒 に
I don't know that speed is the issue
速度が問題であることを私は知りません。
versus reception right I have trouble
対受付権困った
getting a good solid Wi-Fi connection
良い固体のWi-Fi接続を取得
that doesn't drop yes yeah and I'm very
それはええそう下がらない と私は非常によ
very close to the router so I don't like
私は好きではないので、ルータに非常に近い
that so with 5g traditionally anyways
とにかく伝統的に5g
your
きみの
get less coverage that's correct but
少ない報道を受けることは正しいが
better speed mm-hmm so how is this going
mm-hmmより速いスピードです。
to impact performance I can't really be
パフォーマンスに影響 を 与える
sure yet until we've got our hands on
私達が私達の手に入るまで確かにまだ
one of them we can take a look and give
そのうちの1つ を 見てみる ことができ ます
it a try but theoretically we're gonna
試してみますが、 理論的には
get better speed out of the Wi-Fi as
Wi-Fiの速度を上げる
well yes now the exciting thing about
ええ、 今ではエキサイティングなこと
this is even though that they've
これは 彼らが持っ てい た としてもです
announced it this week it's probably
今週それを発表した
gonna take a little bit before we start
始める前に 少し時間がかかります
seeing it for purchase yeah well it is
購入のためにそれを見て ええよくそれ はです
available to buy right technically but I
技術的に正しく購入することができますが、私は
think stock is going traditionally with
株価 は 伝統的に
raspberry pi it is and and maybe this is
ラズベリーパイ ですね
a good chance to remind those who were
た人々 を思い出させるために良いチャンス
hating on the Odroid when they were sold
彼らが売られたときにOdroidを嫌う
out and then they brought new stock to
それから彼らは新しい在庫を
Amazon and then they sold out again when
アマゾン、 その後、彼らは 再び完売
when a new raspberry pi comes out
新しいラズベリーパイが出たとき
they've got a manufacturer all these
彼らは、 メーカー 、これらすべてを 持っています
boards and they've got to get them into
ボードと彼らはそれらを得るために持っています
the stores they've got to get them
彼らがそれらを得るために持っている店
available on other various Amazons and
他の様々なアマゾンで利用可能 と
so they are available technically but
だから彼らは技術的に利用可能ですが
you're probably not gonna actually have
あなたはおそらく実際に持っているつもりはないです。
access to them for a little while we'll
しばらくの間それらにアクセスします
see kind of how that plays out if you do
あなたがそうするなら それがどのように演じるかの種類を見てください
get your hands on one though within the
内 でも 一方であなたの手を得る
next couple of weeks you are one of the
週の次のカップル あなたが の一つ です
the lucky few and we want to hear all
幸運な少数 と私達はすべてを聞きたいです
about it
それについて
mm-hmm all right so what are we talking
mm-hmm大丈夫ですので、何 を 話しているの でしょうか。
about pi should I take a look at the
PIについての私が見てみる 必要があります
Raspberry Pi 3 b-plus sure website so
ラズベリーパイ3 のB-プラスしてくださいウェブサイト ので、
okay head on over to Raspberry Pi organ
大丈夫ラズベリーパイオルガンに向かいます
we're gonna do a lot of stuff on our on
私たちは私たちの上で多くの ものをやるつもりです
our computer here tonight the raspberry
私達のコンピューターは今夜 ラズベリーです
so one of the key things with the B+ is
だからB +の重要なことの一つは
that they are intending to sell it for
彼らはそれを販売しようとしていること
the same price as the B the Raspberry Pi
Bラズベリーパイ と同じ価格
3 so now they say $35 we live here in
3だから今彼らは私たちがここに住んでいる35ドルを言う
Canada I wish that we could get that
カナダ私たち が それを 手に入れること ができれ ば いいのに
kind of a deal y'all Americans are
アメリカの人々は
saving some money we pay a fair bit more
いくらかのお金を節約する
than that up here yes so we talked about
それよりはここにあります
oh and it looks like we've got 802 11
おお、それ は私たちが802 11を持っているよう に 見えます
and see that's good Bluetooth 4.2 Oh
そしてそれは良い Bluetooth 4.2ああ それを参照してください
beautiful
綺麗な
so we may have good good Wi-Fi after all
だから結局のところ良いWi-Fiがあるかもしれません
that's good here's another exciting
これはいいね
thing power over ethernet that's
イーサネット経由のもののパワー
something that Raspberry Pi has been
ラズベリーパイがしたこと
lacking mm-hmm okay power over ethernet
イーサネットで mm-mm mm大丈夫な電源 がない
means you don't have to have separate
あなたが別に 持っ ている必要がないこと を意味します
power you can actually power the device
あなたが実際にデバイスに電力を供給することができます電力
from your router yes so you plug in the
あなたのルーターからそうそうあなたは差し込みます
ethernet cable and it will get its power
イーサネットケーブルとそれはその力を得ます
from the ethernet now there's a caveat
イーサネットから今警告があります
okay one power over ethernet is not yet
大丈夫 、イーサネット上の1つの電源はまだありません
available
利用可能
is coming soon for the pi3 b+ - it
もうすぐpi3 b +の登場です - それは
requires a separate hat which is an
ある別の帽子が必要です
accessory component that you add to the
あなたが追加付属部品
board so there's probably some cost
ボードなので多少の 費用がある
involved in that and three that board
それと3つのその板にかかわった
requires non passive cooling so you're
非受動冷却が必要なので
looking at adding a moving fan to your
動いているファンをあなたに追加しようとしています
Raspberry Pi rig so it's not it's no
ラズベリーパイのリグなのでダメじゃない
longer gonna fit into the Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイに収まるよ
case I'm sure cases are gonna come out
事件が出てくると確信している
with the hat in mind but you do have to
帽子を念頭に置いて、あなたはする必要があります
buy that separately and it's not
別に購入するのではない
currently available so that said I
現在利用可能なので、私は言った
wanted to draw your attention to
あなたの注意 を引きたいと思った
something that I've been looking at and
私が見てきた何かと
I actually ordered yesterday not knowing
私は実際に は知らずに昨日注文しました
that this was coming out when I look at
私が見 た ときにこれが出てき たこと
NEMS Nagios Enterprise management's
NEMS Nagiosエンタープライズ管理
monitoring server which is NEMS
NEMSである監視サーバー
linux.com I was looking for an ability
linux.com 私は能力を探していました
to do power over ethernet so I don't
イーサネット を介して電力を供給する ために
have to have separate power and there is
別々の力を持っている必要があります
in fact this $10 dongle that you can get
実際に あなたが得ることができる この 10ドルのドングル
for your Raspberry Pi oh and it turns
あなたのラズベリーパイのためにああ、それは変わります
Power over Ethernet into Ethernet and
イーサネットから イーサネット への パワーオーバー
five volt and this is 2.4 amp so you've
5ボルト、これ は2.4アンペアなので
got more than enough power here to power
力に十分な力よりもここに得た
a Raspberry Pi or in the screenshots
ラズベリーパイまたはスクリーンショット
that shows that running their Raspberry
それは彼らのラズベリーを実行していることを示しています
Pi with the with the screen and so power
画面とそう力でとパイ
over ethernet is in fact available for
イーサネット経由は実際に利用可能です
the older generation raspberry PI's oh
古い世代のラズベリーPIのああ
that's awesome
それはすごい
and it's super cheap ten dollars and 89
そしてそれは超安い10ドルと89
cents u.s. so I picked up one of those
私達をセントにする ので私はそれらの一つを手に入れた
it's on its way and I'll have that soon
それは途上にあります、そして、私はすぐにそれを持ちます
so you may not have to buy that
だからあなたはそれ を購入 する必要はないかもしれません
Raspberry Pi hat with the fan and
ファンとラズベリーパイの帽子と
everything else
他のすべて
this is 2.4 amp I believe the Raspberry
これは私がラズベリーを信じる 2.4アンペアです
Pi 3 B+ is going to require 2.5 so I'm
Pi 3 B +には2.5が必要になるので、私は
not sure if this adapter I'm not sure
このアダプタ私はよく分からないかどうかわからない
yet if this adapter will support the the
それでもこのアダプタ が
B+ the time will tell as we get those in
我々 はそれらを取得するよう B + 時間が教えてくれる
and start doing some testing right ok so
正しいテスト を始めましょう。
power over ethernet is definitely
イーサネット経由の電力は間違いなく
something that's going to be helpful
役立つ こと になるだろう何か
especially if you're using raspberry
特にラズベリーを使用している場合
PI's in a server environment server
サーバー環境サーバー内のPI
rooms like if you're using them's Linux
Linuxを使っているかのような部屋
for example that's fantastic
例えばそれは素晴らしいです
if you're using it for any anything like
あなたがのような何かのためにそれを使っているなら
plex Pi is another example where hey you
プレックスPiはちょっとあなたに別の例です
just it just cuts down on the cable
ケーブルを切り落とすだけ
clutter I guess
雑然としている
what else have we got oh goodness
他に何があったか
I'm just looking over the list here
ここでリストを見ているだけです
folks USB mass-storage booting so that
USB大容量ストレージのブート
means we no longer have to hack up the
ハッキングする必要がなくなったことを意味します。
SD card to boot from the SD card and
SDカードから起動するSDカード
then from the USB Drive you'll be able
その後、USBドライブから できる ように なります
to boots directly from a USB Drive so
USBドライブから 直接起動するので、
which is very nice very nice indeed
本当にとても素敵です。
because like the SD cards are not very
SDカードのようではないので
reliable if if your Raspberry Pi server
あなたのラズベリーパイサーバーなら信頼できる
system ever fails it's most likely the
システムは、これまでそれが最も可能性があります失敗します
the SD card that's going to be the one
1になるだろう SDカード
that failed so by taking that off of
それ をやめ て失敗し た
there now I'd like to see if you can
今そこに私はあなたができるかどうかを確認したいのですが
boot without an SD card oh that so
SDカードなしで起動 する
that's a great upgrade it's got improved
それはそれが改善された素晴らしいアップグレードです
thermal management it's overclockable
熱管理それはオーバークロック可能です
and finally we're starting to see some
そしてついに私たちはいくつかを見始めています
thermal management on the Raspberry Pi 3
ラズベリーパイ3の熱管理
the the original 3 didn't really have a
元 3は本当にありませんでした
lot of settings so right I'm looking
たくさんの設定が正しい
forward to seeing what RasPi config
何RasPiの設定を見るのを楽しみにして
introduces for this particular board so
この特定のボードのために紹介します
all in all a great step up for Raspberry
ラズベリーにとって大きなステップアップ
Pi users something that we can upgrade
Piユーザーがアップグレードできるもの
to of course everything's still backward
もちろん、すべてがまだ後方にある
compatible so as new software comes out
新しいソフトウェアが出てくるので互換性がある
and everything you don't have to rush
急ぐ必要がないすべて
out and buy the latest and greatest but
うち、 最新かつ最高のが、を 買います
if you want those extra features or
追加機能が必要な場合
because the price is still the same
価格はまだ同じだから
crappy erratically right then you you
安っぽい不規則右 次にあなたあなた
can buy the upgraded version next time
次回アップグレード版を購入することができます
you go around I mean I I I have
私は IIIが持っている という意味
raspberry PI's all around I've got three
ラズベリーPIのすべての周り私は3つ持っています
or four of them hooked up at home at all
またはそれらのうちの4つは まったく 家に引っ掛かった
times extras that I have laying around
私の周りに敷設している倍の追加料金
that I use for various projects and
さまざまなプロジェクトに使用して
everything else so but I'm excited
他の すべて そうそう私は興奮している
mostly I think about the Gigabit
ほとんど私はギガビットについて考える
Ethernet yes did we talk about
イーサネットはい、 話しましたか
availability yes we did ok yes as we
空室状況 はい私たちは私たちとしてOKはい
celebrate Pi Day this week I wanted to
私が し たかった 今週 円周率の日を祝います
kind of go over some of the project
この種のプロジェクト のいくつか の上に行きます
ideas that we've had and some of the the
我々が持っていたアイデアといくつかの
things that you can do with this little
あなたがこれでできること
itty-bitty micro computer ok because the
かなりの数の マイクロ コンピュータ
the projects that you can do with this
あなたが これを行うことができますプロジェクト
are endless oh yeah and that's why it
そうそう無限であり、それは なぜそれが です
has such a following that's why it's
それはそのような理由です
such an exciting project the Raspberry
このような刺激的なプロジェクト、ラズベリー
Pi project itself and why so many people
Pi プロジェクト自体 となぜそんなに多くの人々
are on that bandwagon and why so many
その時流 にあり 、なぜこれほど多くの
people
人
have them first of all episodes 544 and
すべてのエピソード544とそれらの最初にそれらを持っています
545 of category 5 technology TV you know
知っている カテゴリー 5 テクノロジーテレビの 545
those ones because it just happened two
それは2つだけ起こった からです
weeks ago and the week before that we
週間前と 、 我々 の前の週
talked about Plex pie yes Lex pie allows
プレックスパイについて語ったはい
you to turn your Raspberry Pi 3 into a
ラズベリーパイ3を
plex media server and by doing that
プレックスメディアサーバーとそれ を行うことによって
you're able to stream your media and
あなたはメディアを ストリーミングすることができますし、
again if you can put a Gigabit Ethernet
ギガビットのイーサネットを置けば再度
in there you're gonna get better
そこにあなたは良くなるつもりです
performance out of that altogether
その うちのパフォーマンスを 完全に
hmm so I'm excited to see how that goes
うーんので、私はそれ が どのように 行くの か見て興奮している
and Plex pie has been doing very very
そして プレックス パイは 非常に非常にしています
well since we introduced it I love plex
私達がそれを導入してからよく私はプレックスが大好き
pie head on over to our website it's
当社のウェブサイト に それはだ 上 でのパイヘッド
category 5 dot TV and I'd like to show
カテゴリ 5ドットテレビと私は表示したいのですが
you a couple of features here that are
ここにいくつかの機能 があります
going to be helpful for you if you hit
あなたがヒットした場合あなたの ため に 役立つだろう
search and just type in Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイ での検索とだけタイプ
you're gonna get a list of all the
あなたはすべてのリストを取得するつもりです
episodes where we have thought to notate
私たちは記譜すると考えられてきたエピソード
it as pertaining to the Raspberry Pi ok
それ ラズベリーパイ OK に関連するとして
so you can find all that now if you're
あなたがいるなら今、あなたは今 それらすべて を 見つけることができます
looking for covered it a lot oh yeah
探している
we've covered a lot there's four pages
4ページあります
of it so there's certainly a lot of
それで、確かにたくさん あります
content with regards to Raspberry Pi but
Raspberry Piに関するコンテンツ
I'm talking about episodes 544 and 545
第544 話 と第545 話について話している
so what you do is you can go to shows
だからあなたがすることはあなたがショーに行くことができるということです
category 5 technology TV full episodes
カテゴリー5テクノロジーTVの全エピソード
and you need to find the season I know
そして、 あなたは 私が知っている季節を見つける 必要があります
that those ones are in season 11 so you
それらがシーズン 11にあるので
just kind of scroll down and it says
ちょっとスクロールダウンして言う
episode 545 so that is one of the
エピソード545それでそれはの1つです
episodes that we're recommending that
我々は それを推奨 しているエピソード
you check out using Plex PI as a
として Plex PIを 使用してチェックアウトします。
personal media server the one before
パーソナルメディアサーバー
that is episode 544 Plex on a Raspberry
それはラズベリーのエピソード544プレックスです
Pi 3 so I'm going to show you a little
Pi 3だから少しお見せしましょう
hack here to save you having to try to
あなたがしようとしなければならないのを防ぐためにここにハックしてください
find episodes on our website because as
として私たちのウェブサイト上のエピソードを見つける
we tell you about these projects some of
我々は、 これらのプロジェクトについて のいくつかを あなたに伝えます
them may make you go oh I'd love to try
彼らはあなたが行かせるかもしれません私は試してみたいです
that on my Raspberry Pi but then you've
その 私のラズベリーパイ の が、その後、あなたがきました
got to go through 11 seasons worth of
の価値は11の季節 を経る ようになりました
video to try to find it no I'm gonna
それを見つけようとするビデオ私はつもりです
make it a little simpler obviously you
明らかにそれをもう少し単純にする
can use the search tool but if you click
検索ツールを使用できますが、 クリックした場合
on any one of our videos and this is
私たちのビデオのいずれかで、これは
remember I'm looking at category 5
カテゴリー 5を見ているのを覚えている
technology TV so not one of the other
テクノロジーテレビなので他のものではない
shows ok and what you'll notice is that
大丈夫を示し、あなたが気づくもの はそれです
up in the address bar we're at category
私たちはカテゴリーにいるアドレスバーに
5 TV slash shows slash Technology slash
5テレビスラッシュスラッシュ テクノロジスラッシュ
episode slash
エピソードスラッシュ
5:45 so if I change that number 5:45 to
5:45だから私 がその 数を 5:45 に 変える なら
any other number it's going to play that
他のどんな数字でもそれをプレイ しようと し ている
episode instead okay okay so as I
私のように代わりにエピソード代わりに大丈夫大丈夫
mentioned these episodes you can use
あなたが使用できるこれらのエピソード を述べました
that knowledge in order to kind of skip
一種のスキップ するための 知識
there really quick Nagios do tell
本当に速い Nagiosが言うことがあります
Nagios enterprise monitoring server aka
Nagios 企業監視サーバー 別名
nameless names Linux now because I got
私は手に入れたので、 名前のない Linuxは今Linux に
the dot-com oh I want the dot-com so I
ドットコムああ私はドットコムが欲しいので私は
had to find a name that was usable right
正しく使える名前を見つけなければならなかった
and I went with names Linux so if you
そして、私は Linuxという名前 を 付けました。
ever doubt that we love raspberry pie
我々は ラズベリー パイが 大好きであることを疑っている
first of all I designed and built Plex
まず最初に、私は Plex を設計して作りました
pie I designed and built NEMS Linux I'm
私はNEMS Linuxを設計、構築しました
constantly creating projects for the
のためのプロジェクトの作成
Raspberry Pi community we've done some
ラズベリーパイコミュニティ
other things that we'll talk about
我々は について 話しましょう他のもの
but MEMS Linux comm check it out that is
しかし、MEMS Linuxはそれを確認しています。
an enterprise level monitoring system so
企業レベルの監視システム
if you head over to NEMS linux comm it's
NEMS linux commに行っ たら
a free distro that you can install in
あなたがインストールすることができます無料のディストリビューション
your Raspberry Pi 3 and how are we doing
あなたの ラズベリーパイ3とどのように私たちはやっている
here so we've got two hundred and twenty
ここで私たちは二百 二十二持っている
some odd Raspberry Pi threes that are
ある奇妙なラズベリーパイ
running it right now 244 users that are
ある 今 、それを実行している 244人のユーザー
actively checking in every day and it
積極的に毎日のチェックインと それ
shows a little bit of stats here but
ここに少しの統計が表示されますが
essentially what nems Linux is is well
基本的にはLinuxが 何であるかということは問題あり ません
if you're familiar with Nagios it is a
あなたがNagiosに精通しているならば、それはです
monitoring system for your network so
ので 、あなたの ネットワーク のための システムを監視
through this you can tell if something's
これを通して、あなたは何かがあるかどうかを知ることができます
wrong with one of your computers on your
あなたのコンピュータの 1台 に問題があります
network you can tell if there's
あるかどうかを確認できるネットワーク
something going on with like if there's
あるかのように何かが起こっている
a problem so if a server is failing or a
サーバーに障害が発生した場合、または
hard drive is failing here we've got a
ハードドライブが故障しています
sample that c drive space is low on the
C ドライブ の容量がが不足している ことをサンプル
windows server so it's set off an alarm
それ はアラームを オフに設定されて いる ので、Windowsサーバー
and what's neat about is that it'll send
そしてきちんとしているのはそれが送信するということです。
out email notifications it will bring
それがもたらす電子メール通知を出す
them up in your browser if you're
あなたがブラウザの場合は
looking at the interface NEMS linux is a
インターフェースNEMS linuxを見ると、
free tool to turn your Raspberry Pi 3
ラズベリーパイ3を回すための無料ツール
into a network monitoring system mm-hmm
ネットワーク監視システムmm-hmmに
you may wonder ok well I've only got
あなたは大丈夫だけでなく、私が唯一持っている不思議に思うかもしれません
three computers on my network so what
私のネットワーク上の3台のコンピュータ だから何
good is that to me you can set it up to
良いことは 私にはあなたがそれを設定することができるということです
also monitor mom and dad's place and you
また、 ママとパパの 場所とあなたを 監視 します
can set it up to monitor your
あなたを監視するためにそれを設定することができます
customers on their site from one central
自分のサイト上の1つの中央からの顧客
raspberry-pi you can be connecting out
ラズベリーパイあなたが接続することができます
through the internet and checking stats
インターネットを通じて、 統計をチェックする
on various hardware that's on the
上のさまざまなハードウェア上
internet I did not know that
インターネット私はそれを知りませんでした
hmm and then you can use it also to
うーん 、それからあなたもそれを使用することができます
monitor your website see if your website
あなたの ウェブサイト を監視する
is getting a high ping or if it's down
pingが高い、または停止している場合
and it will notify you in those
そしてそれはそれらのあなたに通知します
situations you can even monitor things
あなた も 物事を 監視する こと ができます状況
like a minecraft server and if if it's
Minecraftサーバーのように
getting to be you know too high of CPU
あなた がCPUの高すぎる ことを 知っているようになる
usage warned you things like that it'll
用法はあなたに それが するようなことを警告した
tell you how many players are playing on
何人のプレイヤー がプレイしているか教えてください
your map and there is a limitless amount
あなたの地図と無限の量があります
of stuff that you can do with an immense
あなたが計り知れないことでできることの
Linux server it's incredible so if you'd
Linuxサーバは、それは信じられないですので 、あなたがしたい 場合
like to check out our coverage on NEMS
NEMS に関する 記事 をチェックしたい
Linux of course go to our website
Linuxはもちろん 私たちのウェブサイトに 行き ます
category five dot TV into a search for
カテゴリ 5 ドットテレビの検索に
NEMS nem asks and the reason that I
NEMS nemが尋ねる理由 と私が
would say to search for it is because
それが あるため であるために検索すると言うでしょう
over time we're going to be doing a lot
時間が経つにつれて 私たちはたくさんすることになるでしょう
more features with NEMS because it is
それがある のでNEMSとの より多くの機能
getting very very popular mm-hmm and
非常に非常に人気の MM-HMMを取得し、
I've got some things that I'd love to
私は私がしてみたい いくつかのことを持っています
tell you right now tonight but I can't
今今夜 あなたに言うが、私はできません
see kind of embargoed like there are
あるような禁輸のようなものを参照してください
some announcements coming out in the
で発表されるいくつかの発表
next two weeks really are huge for us
今後2週間は 本当に 私たちにとって 巨大です
ok so names Linux is about to take off
大丈夫 そう Linuxが離陸しようとして いるという名前
buy stocks folks buy stock and and
株式を買う人々が株式 を 買う そして
that's an exciting thing so I say do a
それは刺激的なことな ので、 私は言う
search for names on our website because
当社のウェブサイトで名前を検索する
you're gonna find more content than we
あなたは私たちよりも多くのコンテンツを見つけるつもりです
have there right now so changing that up
今そこにいるので、それを変える
in the top here category five dot TV
ここ の一番上の カテゴリ 5ドットテレビ
slash shows slash technology slash
スラッシュはスラッシュ 技術を 示し ますスラッシュ
episode and the NEMS feature that we did
エピソードと私たちがしたNEMSの 機能
Jeff if you remember it was 478 so if
あなたがそれを覚えているならジェフは 478だったので
you just change that to 478 it should
それを478に変更するだけです。
take us to Nagios enterprise monitoring
Nagiosエンタープライズモニタリングに連れて行って
on a Raspberry Pi 3 and that's gonna
ラズベリーパイ3で、それはするつもりです
start the the episode with us cool Wow
私たちと一緒にエピソードを始めて くださいクールWow
we were good looking then we're good
私たちは見ていて良かった
looking now just look at that got a
今見ているだけでそれを見て
better camera now I know we're kind of
より良いカメラ今私たちは親切 だ
stretched out of out of shape there a
そこ形状のうちの伸ばし
little bit this is the 4k camera that we
少しこれ は 私たちが4Kカメラです
are saving up to purchase so buy a
購入するために貯蓄しているので買う
t-shirt buy a sweatshirt that'll help us
Tシャツは私たちを助けるでしょうスウェットシャツを買う
to do that other projects that you can
その あなたができる こと を 他のプロジェクトを行うには
think of Jeff that we could
私達ができる と ジェフ を考えなさい
do with a Raspberry Pi or that we have
ラズベリーパイまたは 我々が持っていることをやります
done with a Raspberry Pi well there's
ラズベリーパイでできている
lots we've done but one that's on my you
私たちがやったことはたくさんありますが、そのうちのひとつ
know PI bucket list so to speak and I
いわば私はPIバケットリストを知っています
have some of the components at home is
自宅での部品の一部が持っています
to create a pi video game system not not
ではないパイのビデオゲームシステムを作成する
for your TV but old school with the like
あなたのテレビのための ようなもののある 古い学校
an arcade yeah like an arcade joystick
アーケードジョイスティックみたいなアーケード
the buttons so I have a main box or yes
ボタンな のでメイン ボックスがあります。
so I've ordered the buttons and the
だから私は ボタンと
joysticks nice so I have those I just
ジョイスティックが素敵な ので、私はちょうど私がそれらを持っている
fell haven't built the case for it to go
それが進行するためのケースを構築していません
in and I don't want write a tabletop I
と私は卓上を書きたくない私は
want a stance I want a full-size as I've
私がきた ように 、私は フルサイズが 欲しいのスタンスをしたいです
told you you need to put this in the
あなたがこれを置く必要があると言った
garage no I am slowly clearing a spot
ガレージなし スポットをゆっくり片付けている
out where it's like oh what are we gonna
それ が どんな所にあるの か
do with this corner of this room I just
私はちょうど この 部屋の このコーナーでやる
don't know sweetheart
恋人がわからない
the the china cabinet I don't know it
食器棚私はそれを知らない
just exploded do you really need a
爆発しただけで 本当に必要 です か
kitchen table so that's on my list
キッチンテーブルな のでそれが私のリストにあります
definitely and we've looked at some of
間違いなく、私たちはいくつかを見てきました
the gaming potential in the Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイのゲームの可能性
3 we set up retropie yes and what that
3 私たちは レトロとはいそれ を設定し ました
is this it allows you to use now in our
これはあなた が私たちの中で今 使用 することを可能に します
demonstration we used PlayStation 3
PlayStation 3 を 使った デモ
controllers yes they're bluetooth yep
コントローラはい、彼らはブルートゥース yepです
the PlayStation 3 uses bluetooth to
プレイステーション3は、Bluetoothを使用して
communicate with its controllers so you
そのコントローラと通信するので、あなたは
get some controllers for a Playstation 3
プレイステーション3のためのいくつかのコントローラを取得
and you can connect it wirelessly to
そしてあなたはそれを無線で接続することができます
bluetooth on your Raspberry Pi it's
それはですあなたのラズベリーパイの上にブルートゥース
built-in and what was great about that
作り付けとそれについて素晴らしかった
is there is a bunch of different gaming
別のゲームがたくさんありますか
systems on the retropie yeah like
レトロコピー上のシステム
Nintendo Entertainment System Super
ニンテンドーエンターテイメントシステムスーパー
Nintendo place Atari 2600 yes like
任天堂アタリ2600はい好き
totally retro here Absalom and and the
完全にレトロなここAbsalomとそして
PlayStation the original PlayStation one
プレイステーション元プレイステーション1
which the games are actually quite good
ゲームは実際にはかなり 良いです
like if you want to play some original
あなたがいくつかのオリジナルをプレイしたい場合のように
tomb raider there's air that's cool and
墓侵入者涼しい空気がある
using the playstation controller did not
プレイステーションコントローラを使用していませんでした
hamper the gaming at all I mean butter
私はバターを意味する全くゲームを妨げる
well yeah because you can configure
ええ、あなたが設定できるので
within the settings for each system the
各システムの設定内
buttons so when you think of the
あなたが 考える ときにボタンがそう
Nintendo controller you've got the a B
あなたが持っているニンテンドーコントローラA B
up down left right that's it
左上右下それだけです
when you go to the PlayStation 3
あなたがプレイステーション3に行くとき
controller you've got buttons everywhere
どこにでもボタンがあるコントローラー
but it still works and that's a great
それでもまだ動作し、 それは素晴らしいです
thing about retropie the FEU is like Spy
FEUは スパイ のようなものです retropieについて の事
Hunter and instantly just like lamb
狩人と即座にちょうど 子羊のように
chops I'm you know it I dunno it Oh
私はあなたが私は ああ、 それを知らないことを知っているよチョップ
retro gaming for the win ok how many
勝利のためのレトロなゲーム[ ok]
arcade days did I spend playing Spy
アーケードの日は私はスパイをして過ごしましたか
Hunter question is how much did you lose
ハンターの質問はあなたがどれだけ失ったのですか
in court you don't want to know I've
法廷で あなたは 私が知りたく ない
mentioned this in the show no.not
ショーno.notで これを述べた
quarters oh I was an idiot child oh no
四半期 ああ 、私は ああ、いや 馬鹿子供 でした
my back before we had Bitcoin parents
私たちがBitcoinの両親を持つ前の私の背中
would invest in collectible coins for
のための収集コインに投資します
their children oh no no no no and I was
子どもいいえいいえいいえああ、私がいました
young and naive and I didn't know the
若くて素朴で、私は知りませんでした
difference between a coin whose cover
そのカバーのコインの違い
value was $1 but actual value was 3000 I
値は$ 1でしたが、実際の値は 3000 I でした
think I made the arcade very happy but
私はアーケードをとても幸せにしたと思うが
they weren't on and it's honest enough
彼らはオンではなかった、 それは 十分に 正直です
to say oh no no no we can't take that
私たちはそれを 取ること はできません
don't don't bring that here no instead
ここに持ってこないでください
they cash those silver dollars and turn
彼らはそれらの銀のドルを現金にして回します
them into quarters for me I've just
それらを私はちょうどきた私のために宿舎へ
hurts
痛い
ya hurts to hear ok so as we talk about
yaは 私達が について 話す ように、[OK] 聞くのが痛いです
retropie again you can search our web
もう一度お試しくださいあなたは私たちのウェブを検索することができます
site you're gonna find more content
より多くのコンテンツを見つけるつもりのサイト
there but the the key episode was 442 so
そこの しかし主なエピソードは そう442だった
if you changed that address bar head on
そのアドレスバーを変更した場合
over to episode number 440 to build your
あなたを構築するためにエピソード番号440に渡って
own retro gaming console with raspberry
ラズベリーと独自のレトロなゲーム機
pi love that episode we've got so much
パイは、 私たちがそんなに持っているエピソードを愛し
great content on our website folks like
私たちのウェブサイト上の素晴らしいコンテンツ
this this is a little bit of a like
これは少し似ている
throwback to some of the things that we
私達が持っていることのいくつかに先送り
do here over the course of 11 seasons
11の 季節の間にここにし なさい
but a good refresher for you to say hey
あなたが ちょっと 言う ために良いリフレッシュ
I'm getting into Raspberry Pi I'd love
ラズベリーパイ が好きです
to buy one especially now that the PI 3
特にPI 3を購入する
B+ is out
B +が出ている
so what can I do with it we've got a lot
私はそれで何ができるか、私たちは多くのことを持っています
of great content for you yep retro
あなたのための素晴らしいコンテンツのレトロ
gaming is definitely one of them
ゲームは間違いなくそのうちの一つです
oh yeah yeah and I know Sasha's got one
ああそうだねそして私はSashaが持っていることを知っている
and her and Dave absol all the time so
そして彼女とDaveは ので 、すべて の時間を アブソル
yeah they've got it hooked up to a 60
ええ彼らはそれを 60 までフックしてもらった
inch 4k TV I never played and they're
私がプレイしたことがないと彼らは
playing big they're playing
大きく遊んでいる彼らが遊んでいる
yeah like Mario Kart yes no things like
以下のような 無物事はイエスマリオカートのようなええ
that that's all Spy Hunter you know we
それがあなたが 私たち を知っ ているすべてのスパイハンターです
also did a personal web server yeah a
また、パーソナルWebサーバーをやった
couple different episodes sure we did
私達がしたことを確かに カップルの異なったエピソード
so that was going back for 28 ish
だからそれは 28 ishの ために戻っていた
something like that so think about web
そのようなものなので 、Webについて 考え ます
hosting
ホスティング
yeah I'm needing to have a web server to
うん私はにWebサーバーを持っている必要があります
put a website on well you can actually
あなたが実際にすることができます上にウェブサイトを置く
turn a Raspberry Pi 3 or even a earlier
ラズベリーパイ3またはそれ 以前のものを 有効にする
generation Raspberry Pi into a lamp
ランプへの世代ラズベリーパイ
stack or a Linux Apache MySQL PHP web
スタックまたはLinux Apache MySQL PHP Web
server mm-hmm you just plug this in and
サーバーmm  - うーんあなたはこれを接続するだけで
now with the capability of doing power
今の電力を行うための機能を持ちます
over ethernet it becomes even better
イーサネット上ではさらに良くなります
because you get into the network open up
あなたがネットワークに入っ てきたから
the port in the firewall make sure you
ファイアウォールのポートは、 あなたのことを確認してください
change your default password and then
デフォルトのパスワードを変更してから
you're up and going yep okay so which
君は立ち上がって大丈夫だから
episode was that Jeff for 28 there was
エピソードは 28のための ジェフ があったという ことでした
also for 33 but ultimately episode for
また33のためのしかし最終的にのためのエピソード
40 was like okay so let's look at what
40 大丈夫だったので、何を見てみましょう
the difference is here so for 28
違いは28のためにそうここにあります
raspberry pi as a development web server
開発Webサーバーとしての ラズベリーパイ
part one what do we look like back then
その1当時の私たちはどのように見えますか
oh my god you had hair we were just
おお、私の神よ、髪の毛があった
children and I would I was spiky head
子供たちと私はとがった頭だっただろう
nice okay so for 48 and what was the
それでは 48で いいです ね。
next one for was that was 2015 Wow
次の1つは2015年のWowでした
for 33 was green so that would probably
33は 緑だったのでそれはおそらく
be part two yeah of our feature about a
aについての私達の特徴の 2つの 部分になる
development web server
開発Webサーバー
oh it's Kelsey oh I miss Kelsey you
ああそれはKelseyああ私はKelsey あなたがいなくて寂しい
turned into Kelsey ages I know
私が知っているKelsey時代に変わった
yeah nice okay last one was 440 so 440
うんいい大丈夫 最後の1つは 440だった440
is the cat's pajamas head on over there
猫のパジャマは向こうにあります
the cat's pajamas that's it
それだ 猫のパジャマ
I Raspberry Pi lamp stack in 30 minutes
30分で ラズベリーパイ ランプスタック
oh yeah look at that
ええオハイオ州 を見て います
this is 440 we've got Shelley they're
これは440 Shelleyだ。
nice so you can build a Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイを作る ことができます
lamp stack in 30 minutes what that's
30分でランプスタック
quick yeah it's neat about the Raspberry
早速ラズベリーがきれい
Pi isn't it yeah it's super quick quick
Piはないが、それはええ、それは速い超速いです
stuff and I do love that it's just get
ものと私はそれがちょうど得ることが大好きです
it up and going a big part of that Jeff
その ジェフの 大部分を占める
is projects like UC Plex PI right what
UC Plex PIのようなプロジェクトは正しいのです か。
have we done we've created the project
我々はプロジェクトを作成しました行っています
we've given it to you as an image so
画像としてあなたに渡しました
then you just burn it to your card
それからあなたはあなたのカードに それ を 燃やす
mm-hmm stick it in there and turn it on
mm-hmmはそこにそれを貼り付けて電源を入れます
yeah and you're done so you you're
ええ 、あなたは終わったのであなたはあなた
really up and going really quick now
本当に上がって、そして今すぐ速くなって
with a Raspberry Pi lamp stack instead
ラズベリーパイランプスタック付き
what we did is showed you how to use
我々がしたことはあなたに使い方を見せられた
Debian or raspbian and then build the
Debianまたは ラズビアンを作成してから
packages on top of that to build that
それを構築するためのそれの上のパッケージ
lamp stack or a Linux Apache MySQL PHP
ランプスタックまたはLinux Apache MySQL PHP
web server and run it on this and I've
Webサーバーとこれでそれを実行し、私は
got raspberry PI's that I've been
ラズベリーのPIを持って いる
running 24/7 since that date and still
その日から24時間365日稼働
running great oh yeah no problem
走っていても大丈夫
whatsoever
何でも
very very no moving part very efficient
非常に非常に効率的な可動部分が非常に効率的
mm-hmm what else can we do we did a
MM-うーん 、私たちは、私たちは他に 何をし たんすることができます
music server oh yeah I was talking about
音楽サーバーええオハイオ州、私が話していました
that recently that was a while ago that
その最近それは少し 前 でした
was back episode for 14 for 16 and for
16の ための 14と14のための バックエピソード でした
25 three-part series so we're talking
25の 3部構成シリーズ
about volumio
ヴォルミオについて
yes so you take your Raspberry Pi 3 and
はい、 ラズベリーパイ3 を
you boot up volumio and what it becomes
あなたはvolumioを起動し、それがどうなるか
is your very own music server so think
あなた自身のミュージックサーバーですか？
about Spotify
Spotifyについて
in the palm of your hands so you get
あなたの手の手のひらにあなたが得る ように、
your own library kind of like how we've
私たちがやってきたような種類のあなた自身のライブラリ
done Plex with video volumio becomes
ビデオvolumioでやったプレックスになる
that for audio specifically but it's
特にオーディオ用ですが
designed specifically for that with the
そのために特別に設計された
interface for that so you can access it
あなたが それに アクセスできるようにするためのインタフェース
on your phone and switch through your
お使いの携帯電話で
music put on your playlist
プレイリストに 入れる音楽
in Sasha's case she's using a Raspberry
Sashaの場合、彼女は ラズベリー を使用しています
Pi 3 hooked up to the PA system at the
Pi 3は、PAシステムに接続し ました。
mat her work okay and from her computer
彼女の作品を大丈夫に そして 彼女のコンピューターから マットする
she accesses it and programs the
彼女は それ にアクセス して
playlist of all the music that they want
彼らが望む すべて の音楽の プレイリスト
to play and then put it on shuffle so
プレイしてシャッフルする
they now have so they just import their
彼らは今持っているので、彼らはただ自分の
music as mp3's from CD or from iTunes or
iTunesの CDからまたはから音楽などのmp3のか
whatever it is that they use and pop it
それが彼らが使用してそれをポップするということは何でも
on there and then they can stream their
そこにそしてそれから彼らはそれらを流すことができます
music to the speakers in a very cool on
非常にクールでスピーカーに音楽を
the clinic what's awesome works a treat
診療所素晴らしいことは何 ですか
so okay those numbers for 14 for 14 yep
それで 14 yepの ための 14のための それらの数
let's see what it tells us and this is
それが私たちに伝えていることを見てみましょう。 これは
one of those series where we actually
私たちが実際に行って いるそれらの シリーズの 1つ
went on site to talk about it - so
それについて話すために現場に行った - だから
there's Sasha and so this was getting us
サーシャ がいるので、これは私たちを得ていた
started
始まった
mm-hm and then for 16 for 16 so we
mm-hmそしてそれから 16のための16のように我々
skipped a week and then for 16 let's see
1週間スキップしてから16年間見てみましょう
where we were so this is raspberry pi
私たちがいたところこれはラズベリーパイです
music server part 2 and I you know it
ミュージックサーバーパート 2 と私はあなたがそれを知っています
could be a quicker project there we are
私たちが いるより速い プロジェクトになるかもしれません
again but I think because of the way
再びしかし私は方法のために考える
that we had set it up we really wanted
私たちは本当にそれを設定したこと
to walk you through all the various
いろいろなところをあなたを歩くために
steps show you how it's done
手順はそれがどのように行われるかをあなたに示します
so we took you all through it there's
それで、私たちはあなたを通してそれをすべて通しました
volume you know running on a Raspberry
あなたがラズベリーで走っているのを知っているボリューム
Pi and what was the third and final
Pi と3番目 で最後のもの
episode 25 or 25 yeah and that is part
第25話または第25話
three simply said crescendo of the music
3つは単に 音楽の クレッシェンド を 言った
server there you go what does this one
そこにサーバーあなたはこれを何をしに行く
look like Oh Hillary okay so where do we
大丈夫 ああヒラリー のように見えるので、どこにやります
go from here alright we actually went on
ここから大丈夫 我々が実際に行った 大丈夫
site to see Sasha connecting this thing
これを つなぐ サーシャを見るサイト
to the PA system and learned all about
PAシステムへとすべてについて学びました
how she's using it how she's got it set
彼女はそれをどのように使用しているか彼女はそれを設定している方法
up we went out into the to the front
私たちは正面に出て行きました
desk area mm-hmm
机の面積 mm-hmm
obviously this was around Christmas time
明らかにこれはクリスマス頃でした
that she's sending this up there's Sarah
彼女がこれを送って いるのは サラだ
one of our friends and so you definitely
私たちの友人の一人で、あなたは 間違いなく
want to check that out learn all about
すべてを学ぶ ことを確認したいです
volumio and using the Raspberry Pi as a
として ラズベリーパイを使用する
music server yeah and some people would
音楽サーバーええと何人かの人々 だろう
say okay well how do you hook up the
大丈夫と言う あなたはどのように接続する の ですか
audio so it's got HDMI output yeah if
オーディオなのでHDMI出力があります
you connect it to a TV it's going to
あなたはそれが起こって テレビに接続します
send the audio out to the TV so
テレビにオーディオを送るので、
typically I use these things headless I
通常私はこれらのことをヘッドレスで使います
never put a monitor on the right you may
あなたがするかもしれない右側にモニターを置かないでください。
want to in some cases but for volumio
いくつかのケースでは 、しかしvolumioのためにしたい
I use the eighth inch output the 3.5
3.5インチの8インチ出力を使用します
millimeter headphone jack and that goes
ミリメートルヘッドホンジャックとそれが行きます
to an RCA splitter into the amp or
RCAスプリッタをアンプに
whatever it is that I'm doing you can
私がやっている ことが何であれあなたはできる
also buy a hat that gives you lossless
無損失の帽子も購入する
audio
オーディオ
it's got optical audio output or RCA
それは光オーディオ出力またはRCAを持っています
audio output if you're more of a hi-fi
あなたがもっとハイファイであればオーディオ出力
fan then that's something that you can
ファン ならそれはあなたができることです
do if you really want to step things up
あなたが本当に物事をステップアップしたい場合はどうしますか
I think it's called hifiberry high-five
私はそれがハイファイブリー ハイファイブと呼ばれると思います
airy yeah you just do a quick search for
エアリーええあなただけの クイック検索を 行う
hi-fi Barre and this is the the
ハイファイバレとこれは、
audiophile component that you can add to
あなたが追加できる audiophile コンポーネント
your Raspberry Pi and it gives you that
あなたの ラズベリーパイとそれはあなたにそれを与える
really good theatrical sound so now your
本当に良い演劇的なサウンド
Raspberry Pi is not just using the the
ラズベリーパイは、単に使用していません
headphone jack output this bad boy gives
この悪い子が与えるヘッドフォンジャック出力
you everything else that looks like an
あなたのように見える他のすべてのもの
amp module it does DSP board digital
アンプモジュールDSPボード デジタル
outs beautiful that's cool there's a
そこの美しいのは、 クールというアウト
bunch of different ones that they carry
彼らが持っているさまざまなものの束
you can also vote them yeah you can find
投票することも できます
them on Amazon what hardware do they do
Amazonで彼らはどんなハードウェアを使っているのか
they have here on their site nice nice
彼らは彼らのサイトにここにあります
Wow there are various different types of
うわー 、さまざま な種類が あります
these kinds of hats that are available
利用可能な これらの種類の帽子
for you that's one of the neat things
あなたのためにそれはきちんとしたことの一つです
about Raspberry Pi 2 is that and I'm
ラズベリーパイ2について
gonna you're gonna catch me all the
あなたは私のすべてを キャッチするつもりだ
times I say here's one of the neat
私はここで言う時間はきちんとしたの1つです
things about Raspberry Pi because
ラズベリーパイについて
there's a lot of great stuff about it
それについて素晴らしいことがたくさんあります
that's again one of the reasons that
それは、再び その 理由の 一つです
it's so popular it's expandable you can
それはとても人気がありますそれはあなたができる拡張可能です
add more components and make it better
より多くのコンポーネントを追加し、それをより良くする
make it do things more specifically for
それが ために、より具体的に物事を行う 作ります
your project the circuit board is
あなたのプロジェクト の回路基板は
literally just that it's the computer
文字通りちょうど それがコンピューターだということ
yeah the brain is animal footprint yeah
ええ脳は動物の足跡ですええ
and then you can do anything else just
それからあなたはただ他に何でもすることができます
by connecting other things to it I know
他のものを接続することによって私は知っています
I've spent time like just searching the
私はただ検索するように時間を費やしました
internet looking at PI projects and
インターネットで PIプロジェクトを見て
there's one I I saw I was so neat and
私はとてもきれいだった 見た 1、私はそこだと
it's you take
それはあなたがかかります
a mirror oh yeah and you or sorry a TV
鏡ああそうそうあなた はテレビを申し訳ありません
screen and you dismantle your TV and so
画面とあなたはあなたのテレビを解体します
you okay you can have a screen on your
あなたは大丈夫あなたは あなたの 上に画面を持つことができ ます
mirror I'm gonna take a little 19 inch
ミラー私は少し19インチを取るつもりです
screen or something put it behind your
スクリーンか 何かがあなたの後ろに置きます
mirror with your PI so that when you get
あなたが得 た ときに そうするようにあなたのPIとミラー
up in the morning using the touchscreen
タッチスクリーンを使っ て朝起きる
you can tell you the weather and all it
あなた は あなたに天気とそのすべてを伝えること が でき ます
was a great project and I'm like oh I
素晴らしいプロジェクトでした。
love this thing and yeah yeah you've got
この事を愛し、ええええ、あなたは持っています
it right there see like you could do
あなたができるようにそれはすぐ そこに見ます
that with a PI that's a Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイだ PIとのこと
powered smart mirror I think that's so
パワードスマートミラー私はそれがそうだと思います
cool
クール
some people are you know these guys are
何人かの人々はあなたがこれらの人たちがいることを知っていますか
brilliant people are always coming up
華麗な人々は 、常に 予定 されています
with new ways to use the Raspberry Pi to
にラズベリーパイを使用 する新しい方法で
do really amazing things I love that one
本当にすごいことをする
I think that's so neat is something I've
私はそれがとてもきれいだ と思うが 、私はきたもの です
wanted to build just haven't had this
これを 持っていなかっ た だけで構築したかった
time and you'd have to be a pretty good
時間とあなたはかなり良い する 必要があると思います
handy person to do that kind yes you are
そのようなことをするのに便利な人そうはいあなたは
I am not so I tend to focus on software
私はそうではない私は ソフトウェア に集中 する 傾向がある
because that's my forte hardware I'm
それが私の強みのハードウェアだから
just kind of learning how to get into
どうやって入るかを学ぶようなもの
that so I've started by learning to
それで、私は 学ぶことから 始め ました
solder and you know some people have
ハンダ付けしている
seen my soldering tutorial videos and
私のはんだ付けチュートリアルビデオを見て
said that's not how I'm learning I'm
それ は私が学ん でいる 方法ではない と言った
just I'm a noob and it's okay and so
ただ私はnoobです、 それは大丈夫ですので
this is my first actual like completed
これが 完成したような 私の最初の 実際のものです
kit project okay so this is not a
これでは ないキットプロジェクト
Raspberry Pi this is a component that
ラズベリーパイこれはそのコンポーネントです
you can use connected to a Raspberry Pi
あなたはラズベリーパイに接続して使用することができます
and it's basically have you ever had
それは基本的にあなたが今まで持っていたことがあります
your internet freeze up yes what do you
インターネットがフリーズする
do when your internet freeze up yeah
あなたのインターネットがええフリーズ時に行います
like the what the modem the modem why do
何モデム何モデムの ように
you do that well to put it through a
あなたはそれを通すためにそれをうまくやる
boot cycle and then does it come right
起動サイクルし、それからそれは正しく来るのですか
back up well 60 seconds to boot up
起動 するだけでなく、60秒を バックアップ
typically yeah and then everything works
通常そうだ そしてそれからすべてがうまくいく
yeah usually so what if you're not home
ええ、たいてい は家に い ないのなら
what if you're on the road and your
あなたが出張中で、あなたの
internet goes down and you know that oh
インターネットがダウンし、あなたは ああ 知っている
if only I could just unplug the power
ただ電源を抜くことができれば
from my modem for just 30 seconds but I
私のモデムからわずか30秒間
don't think you could do that wouldn't
できるとは思わないでください
that be nice though that would be
それ はいいだろうがそれはいいことだ
kicking yourself saying
自分を蹴る
I'm at the hotel in Toronto and I can't
私はトロントのホテル にいます ができません
access my server yeah that stinks so
私のサーバーにアクセス する
what this devices that I did I designed
私が設計したもの
and built and it's very simple this
そして構築され、それはこれは非常に簡単です
plugs into the USB on my router yep okay
大丈夫私のルーターのUSBに差し込む
because routers these days often have a
最近のルータには
USB port yeah external storage or
USB ポート ええ外付けストレージまたは
programming or whatever so I plug this
プログラミングなど何でもそう私はこれを 差し込む
into the usb on the router my modem
私のモデムルータ の USBに
power adapter goes into the the barrel
電源アダプタは バレルに入ります
input here okay and then I've got a
ここに入力して 大丈夫、 それから私は持っている
matching barrel cable that goes into the
入る一致バレルケーブル
modem so this works in both game yep the
モデムなのでこれは 両方のゲームで 動作します
modems power cable and the modem itself
モデム電源ケーブルとモデム自体
yes this goes into my router now I've
はい、 これ は私のルータに入ります
written a program for my router it's a
それはです 私のルータのために書かれたプログラム
micro tech so you can script it that
マイクロテックスクリプトにそれをすることができますので、
says if the internet goes down wait and
インターネットがダウンした場合は待機
it waits for about three minutes if it
それが あれば3分 ほど待つ
still is down and it tries again
まだダウンしています
periodically through those three minutes
これらの3分を通して定期的に
if it's still down after three minutes
3分経ってもまだ停止している場合
power cycle the modem no way yeah so it
モデムの電源を入れ直す方法はありません
actually kills the power it's got a
実際にそれが持っている力を殺します
relay in here yep so the 5 volt gets a
ここではね、5ボルトは
signal and the relay trips turns off the
信号とリレートリップ がオフになります。
12 volt and then turns it back on after
12ボルト、その後それを再びオン にする
30 seconds look at a senate tests again
上院テストをもう一度 見て 30秒
and it sees if the internet is back up
インターネットがバックアップされているかどうか
and wrong so it's basically the the next
そして間違っているので、それは基本的に次の
best thing to be in there at power
力でそこにいるために最高のもの
cycles so this is my first design and
これが私の最初のデザインです
build i built i designed it from from
私はそれを設計しました
like myself yeah I didn't use any
私のように私はどれも使っていない
schematics or anything I made it myself
回路図または自分で作ったもの
and and designed it and built it and
そしてそれを 設計しそしてそれを造ったそして
coded it that's nice oh cool
クールああ 素敵だと 、それをコード化
so but I was thinking about how this is
それで、私はこれがどのようにあるかについて考えていました
just a 5 volt trigger yeah my router ok
ちょうど5ボルトのトリガー うん私のルーター大丈夫
this could go into the USB of a
これはのUSB に 入ることができる
Raspberry Pi and I could do any number
ラズベリーパイと私は何でもすることができます
of things with it right right or instead
それが正しいものの 代わりに
of going USB I could take the the the 2
USBに行くの私は 2を 取ることができる
contacts the leads and go to the GPIO of
リードに連絡してのGPIOに行きます
my Raspberry Pi ok because there's this
私のラズベリーパイOK これがあります ので、
massive GPIO here let's get a little bit
ここでの大規模なGPIOはのは少し取得してみましょう
closer there for you so you see all
あなたのために近くにあるので、あなたはすべてを見る
these pins yeah I can go I can connect
これらの ピンええ 私は行くことができます私は接続することができます
into these pins and be able to program
これらのピンに接続し て プログラムする ことができます
what they do so now all of a sudden I
彼らが今何をしているのか 突然私は
can power cycle my modem
モデムの電源を入れ直すことができます
I can turn on the lights or I can do
私はライトをつけることができますまたは私はすることができます
home automation I can do all kinds of
ホームオートメーション私はすべての種類のことができます
things
物事
powered by the Raspberry Pi and some
ラズベリーパイといくつかによって供給
kind of that's you know even a novice
初心者でも知っていること
can build all right that's cool yeah so
ええとても クールだすべての権利を構築することができます
there's no end to the projects so you
プロジェクトに終わりはない ので、あなたは
can go a full-blown like home alone sure
確かに一人で家のように本格的に行くことができます
yeah great should we jump into if that's
ええ 、それがうまくいけば 素晴らしい
that kind of covers some of the projects
その種の プロジェクト はいくつかの プロジェクト をカバーして います
that we do here yeah let's get into some
ここでやっている こと
viewer questions that have been
されている視聴者の質問
submitted oh yes out the Raspberry Pi
Raspberry Piを投稿しました
and Before we jump right into them so
そして私達が彼らの中に飛び込む前に
we've got your questions thank you for
ご質問ありがとうございます
sending the man we do have to take a
男を送る私たちは取る必要があります
really quick commercial break when we
我々がいる とき本当に速いコマーシャル休憩
come back we're going to talk about
私たちが話をするつもり戻ってきます
we're gonna answer as best we can the
私たちはできる限り最善の答えを得ようとしている
questions that have been submitted to us
私達に提出された質問
about the Raspberry Pi stick around for
ラズベリーパイについて
a limited time get your hands on
限られた 時間で手 をつないで
limited-edition shirts from the category
このカテゴリの 限定版シャツ
5 TV network these high-quality shirts
5テレビネットワーク これらの高品質のシャツ
are manufactured by teespring a
aをteespringすることによって製造されています
fundraising website and your purchase
募金ウェブサイトとあなたの購入
will help support the shows we produce
私達が作り出すショーを支えるのを助けます
get yours today and send us your
今日あなたのものを入手して私たちにあなたのものを送って ください
pictures to be featured on the
で紹介される写真
corresponding show visit cap v dot TV
対応するショー訪問キャップv ドットテレビ
slash shirts to support us and get your
私達を支え、あなたのものを手に入れるためにシャツを切る
official Network shirt today cap v dot
公式ネットワークシャツ今日キャップ vドット
TV slash shirts long back this is
これはテレビのスラッシュシャツの長さです。
category 5 technology TV episode number
カテゴリー5テクノロジーTVのエピソード番号
547 it's so nice to have you here and
547 あなたがここにいるのはとてもうれしいです
tonight as we celebrate pi week we're
今週はパイ週間を祝うので、
calling it but pi day was Wednesday 314
それを呼び出しますが、パイ日は水曜日314でした
and we are celebrating with feature
そして私達は特徴と祝っています
about the Raspberry Pi and so we're
ラズベリーパイについて
about to get into your viewer questions
あなたのビューアの質問に入る ことを約
that have been submitted over the past
過去に投稿されたもの
week or so should we just jump right
一週間かそこらはちょうど 右に ジャンプする必要があり ます
into it
それに
absolutely ok so Rob Gor says a rag or
Rob Gorがボロボロと言っても大丈夫です。
hi Robbie ello I love the episodes on
こんにちは ロビーエロ私は上のエピソードが大好き
setting up Plex on the Raspberry Pi
ラズベリーパイにプレックスを設定する
could you go through the process of
のプロセスを経てもらえますか
setting the PI up so that it can access
アクセスできるようにPIを 設定 する
the media from a server like FreeNAS on
FreeNAS onの ようなサーバーからのメディア
ray Det cetera ah ok so this is
レイDet cetera ああ[OK]これはそうです
something I don't have a server per se
私 はサーバー 自体を 持っていない もの
here at the studio I take our files
ここのスタジオで私はファイルを取ります
off-site and their backdrop off-site so
オフサイトとその背景オフサイト
I don't have any Nass hairs or anything
Nassの髪の毛など何もない
like that that I can demonstrate with
そのように私は実証することができます
but I will tell you here's where things
しかし、私はあなたがここで物事をここで教えてあげる
get exciting with Raspberry Pi with Plex
ラズベリーパイとプレックスでワクワクする
PI and with these kinds of things is
PIとこれらの種類の ものとは
that we don't have to think of it in
私たちはそれについて考える必要はありません
terms Rob Gore as how do we connect to
Rob Goreはどのように接続するのかという用語です。
the NASS with Plex PI how do we connect
プレックス PI とNASSは どのように接続するのです
to the NASS with NEMS
NEMSとNASSへ
how do we connect to the NASS with back
どのように我々は戻っ てNASSに接続しません
up a moment and just think about the
今 まで と だけ考えます
base of Plex PI and nems and raspbian
プレックスPIのベースとnems and raspbian
and all these things
そしてこれらすべてのこと
what are they at their heart their Linux
彼らの核心は何ですか
right right so the question becomes how
そうです、質問 はどうなりますか。
do we connect to a Samba share or CIFS
Samba共有またはCIFSに接続しますか
on Linux and as soon as we understand
Linux 上 とすぐ私たちは理解して
that now we're able to do that on flex
これで 、flexで それが可能になり ました
PI we're able to do that on nems the
PI我々は NEMS 上でそれを行うことができるしています
knowledge supersedes it blankets all of
知識はそれをすべて覆い隠します
those distros because they are all Linux
それらはすべてLinuxなので、これらのディストリビューション
right so I'm going to point you to see
正しいので、私はあなたに 会う ように指示するつもりです
ifs - utils that used to be samba but
ifs  - かつては samba だった utils
now it's CIFS that connects that's the
接続するのはCIFSです
the fuse
ヒューズ
I believe it's fuse but whatever it
私はそれがヒューズだと思いますが、それは何でも
connects to Samba shares network sharing
Samba共有ネットワーク共有に接続する
on your network and it allows you to set
あなたのネットワーク上で 、それはあなたが 設定 することができます
up FS tab entries which is your
あなたのFSタブエントリを
filesystem table that allows you to have
あなたが持つことができるファイルシステムテーブル
those things automatically boot when you
これらのことは自動的に起動します
turn on your computer or when you turn
あなたが電源を入れたとき にコンピュータの電源を入れますか、
on your PI and you're gonna have instant
あなたの PIで、あなたはインスタントを持っているつもりです
access to it let's jump over to our
それへのアクセスは 、私たちに飛び越え てみましょう
website category 5 dot TV into a quick
簡単に ウェブサイトのカテゴリ 5ドットテレビ
search for FS tab I'm gonna try an out
FSタブを検索します。試してみます。
CIFS let's just see if that brings us
CIFS は それが私たちをもたらすかどうかを 見てみましょう
any results here Rob Gor making your
Rob Gorがあなたのものを作る
website faster with cloud-based
クラウドベースで Webサイトを高速化
JavaScript hosting that doesn't sound
JavaScriptホスティングが鳴らない
right okay so let's try CIFS resolving
それでは、 CIFSの解決を 試してみましょう。
host names tracking your projects making
プロジェクトを追跡しているホスト名
your website faster I wonder if we
あなたのウェブサイトより速く 私たちかしら
talked about it in that episode that's
その エピソードで それについて 話しました
why it's come up twice all right now if
次の場合
we're not seeing results for that
その 結果は見ていません
let's try FS tab samba
FSタブsambaを試してみましょう
no luck see I know that we've covered it
私たちがそれをカバーしたことを私は 知っているの を 見る運がない
Rob gore and this is where I kind of
ロブゴアと これは私が好きなところです
tongue-in-cheek say as long as we
冗談は、 私たちと同じくらい長いと言います
remember to tag the episode and maybe
エピソードをタグ付けすることを忘れないでください
that's why that one episode is coming up
その1つのエピソードがやってくるのはそのためです
maybe we did talk about it and so we
多分私達はそれについて話しましたそしてそれで 私達は
tagged it in the in the keywords I'm
私がキーワードでそれをタグ付け
gonna head over instead to mine my blog
代わりに私のブログをマイニングするつもりだ
which is bald nerd calm and try the
はげオタク落ち着いていると試してみてください
search there same search CIFS FS tab oh
そこに同じ検索CIFS FSタブを検索
I got a extraneous space in there but
そこに余分なスペースがありますが
let's see FS tab let's just do that
のは、FSタブが ちょうど それを 行う のを聞かせて見てみましょう
automatically deduplicating data add a
データを自動的に重複排除する
drive to Linux and encrypt it backup a
Linuxにドライブし、バックアップを暗号化する
Linux machine with LVM plex media server
LVMプレックスメディアサーバーを搭載した Linuxマシン
arm Raspberry Pi 3 make it so mount
アームラズベリーパイ 3
point can't be written if it's not
そうでなければ点を書くことはできませ ん
mounted boy oh boy do we move over to
取り付けられた男の子ああ男の子私たちはに移動しますか
Google I know that I've covered all this
Google私はこれをすべて網羅していることを知っています
stuff just where yeah where did I put it
ちょうどどこどこで私は それ を入れまし た
in our cloud of FS tab let's try samba
FSタブの 私達の雲で sambaを 試してみましょう
one last shot no thing found so instead
最後の一発は何も見つからなかった
try CIFS - utils FS tab is what I'm
CIFSを試してみてください-  utils FSタブ が私のものです。
going to search for wiki dot new boom -
wiki dot new boom を検索し ます -
dot-com sounds trustworthy so here you
ドットコムは信頼できるように聞こえます
go
行く
mount windows shares permanently and
恒久的にWindows共有をマウントし、
this takes you through so what we need
これはあなたを通過させます
to do as I mentioned you need to install
私が言ったようにするにはあなたがインストールする必要があります
CIFS utils ok ignore the uh Noldor
CIFSユーティリティ は、ええとNoldorを無視しても大丈夫です
system nobody installs SMB FS anymore
誰もSMB FSをインストールしない
and then mounting so then edit your FS
マウントしてからFSを編集します
tab file and put this in there now
タブファイルとこれを今そこに置く
there's a couple of things that I would
私がすることがいくつかあります
also add let's see if they include it so
彼らがそれを含んでいるかどうかも見てみましょう追加
their first example is a little bit
彼らの最初の例は 少しです
vague so a little bit of research and
曖昧なので少し研究 を
you'll be able to find what you need but
あなたはあなたが必要なものを見つけることができるでしょう
that should get you up and going here's
それはあなたを立ち上げてここに行くべきです
this one looks a little nicer yeah so I
これはもう少しきれいに見えるので、私は
think if anything I'm realizing maybe
私が何かを実現しているのではないかと思う
that's something I should do a feature
それは私が機能をするべきものです
on and I'd be happy to
と私は幸せになります
but this this will give you what you
しかし、これはあなたに何をあなたに与えるでしょう
need to get in order to do that so CIFS
CIFS のでそれを行うため に取得する必要があります
utils FS tab those are your queries
utils FSタブこれらはあなたのクエリです
those are the things that you need to do
これらはあなたがする必要があることです
so essentially with CIFS you're able to
そう基本的にCIFSとあなたができる
mount nash shares on linux and FS tab
Linuxと FSタブに nash共有を マウントする
does it every time you boot but what we
起動するたびにそれを行います
want to do is we want to set it up with
やりたいのは私たちがそれを設定 したいのです
things like so that it knows that it's a
それがそれであることを知っているようなもの
network share and so that it knows not
それを知らないように、ネットワーク共有
to halt your system if it's not
そうでない場合はシステムを停止します
connected on boot those kinds of things
起動時に接続されたもの
so I was sure that I did a feature it's
だから私は それがそれが機能をやった こと を 確信 し ていた
out there somewhere anyone knows or if
誰かが知っている か、または
anyone has been binging category-five
誰もがカテゴリー5をうんざりしている
and has found it please let me know the
そしてそれを 私に 知ら せ て ください
episode that'd be great thanks Rob gory
偉大な おかげでロブ血みどろの だろうエピソード
it's nice - nice to hear from you
それは素晴らしいです - あなた から連絡 をもらって うれしい です
ok orange man writes dear Robbie
大丈夫オレンジ男 は親愛なる ロビーを 書き込みます
I've got Plex PI to work and the only
私は仕事にプレックスPIを持ってきました
thing is that when I try to access the
私がアクセスしようとすると
plex interface through my PC in another
別の私のPCを介してプレックスインターフェイス
room I open Firefox and enter the
私はFirefoxを開いて入る
address HTTP colon front slash 127.0.0.1
アドレスHTTPコロンのフロントスラッシュ127.0.0.1
colon three two four zero zero front
コロン3 2 4 0ゼロフロント
slash web front slash index dot HTML but
WebフロントスラッシュインデックスドットHTMLをスラッシュが、
it didn't work
うまくいかなかった
hmmm what am I doing wrong ok and what
うーん、私は何をして いるの です か？
PS it badly buffers on some films which
PSそれはいくつかの映画でひどく緩衝する
makes it difficult to watch why does it
なぜそれをするのか見るのを難しくします
do this with some videos and not others
他の人 で はなく いくつかのビデオでこれをしてください
first thing I would look at is the codec
私が最初に見 たのはコーデックです。
that's used in those videos for example
それは例えばそれらのビデオで使われています
h.265 requires a lot of CPU in order to
h.265を実行するには多くの CPU が必要です。
decode so make sure your videos are
デコードするので、あなたのビデオが
h.264 that will probably most likely
おそらく最も可能性の高い h.264
will be the issue otherwise if it's a
それ以外の場合 は問題になります
massive file like 4k 120 frames a second
毎秒4フレーム120フレームのような巨大なファイル
it's got a transcode and it's not a
それ はトランスコード を 持っ ています 、そしてそれはそうではありません
these are not that powerful you can
これらはあなたができるほど強力ではありません
understand that so you may need to
あなたがする必要があるかもしれないので、それを理解する
change those files as far as the
これらのファイルを
formatting goes h.264 is probably better
フォーマットはh.264になるでしょう
for you than h.265 for sure back to your
確か に あなたに 戻って H.265よりあなたのために
first comment okay so we've got Plex PI
最初のコメント大丈夫そう私たちはプレックスPIを持っています
up and going on our PI we're trying to
私たちがしようとしている私たちのPIに行って行く
access it by going to HTTP colon slash
HTTPコロンスラッシュを使って アクセスする
slash 127.0.0.1 colon 32400 slash web
スラッシュ127.0.0.1コロン32400スラッシュウェブ
yep so the address is correct only if
うんそうアドレスが場合 にのみ 正確です
you are sitting at your Raspberry Pi why
あなたは、なぜ あなたの ラズベリーパイ の 前 に 座っています
any guesses probably no clue 127.0.0.1
どんな推測もおそらく手がかりがない127.0.0.1
27.0 0.1 is localhost yes on any
27.0 0.1はlocalhostです yes
computer that IP address will refer back
IPアドレスが参照するコンピュータ
to itself so if you are trying to
あなたがしようと し ているのであれば それ自体 に
connect to this system from my laptop
私のラップトップからこのシステムに接続します
and on my laptop I type 127.0.0.1 my
そして私のラップトップ上で私は127.0.0.1私のタイプ
laptop will try to connect to my laptop
ラップトップは私のラップトップ に接続しようとします
not to the PI so what you need is the
何が必要そうPIはありませんに
internal IP address of the PI easiest
最も簡単なPIの内部IPアドレス
way to find that is probably login to
それを見つける方法はおそらくログインです
your router
あなたのルーター
look at the DHCP pool and all of the
DHCPプールとすべての
active devices and you'll see one called
アクティブなデバイスであれば、
Plex PI and that is the entry in your
プレックスPIとそれは あなた のエントリです
DHCP server and it will give you the IP
DHCP サーバーとそれはあなたにIPアドレスを与えるでしょう
address there in your router now most
あなたのルーターのアドレスが一番多い
routers have the default of one ninety
ルーターのデフォルトは1 90です。
two dot one six eight dot zero dot and
2ドット1 6 8ドット ゼロドット
then something yeah so I mean you're
それから何かそうそう私はあなたがいるという意味
probably going to be in that
おそらくその中になるだろう
neighborhood yeah but that's why now if
近所そうだけど、 今なら今 が 理由
you're accessing your Plex PI from
Plex PIにアクセスしています
outside your network though well that's
ネットワーク外でも
a whole different thing let's yes that's
まったく別のことを言え ば そう です
not confused Jeff so no don't do it yeah
Jeffを混同しないでください。
don't don't even try that just within
でも ただの中 のことを しようとしないでくださいしないでください
the network not outside get started in
外部ではないネットワークに入る
the land yes understand that first and
土地はそう最初にそれを理解します
then we'll talk about the rest okay yeah
それから私たちは残りの話をしましょう大丈夫
because then we're getting into a whole
それから私達は 全体に入っ ています
other can of worms and port forwarding
他のワーム やポート転送の可能性
and everything else we don't want to get
そして私たち が得たくない 他のすべて
into that tonight for orange man so
オレンジ色の男のためにその今夜 にそう
orange man find the IP address of this
オレンジ色の男はこれの IPアドレスを見つける
if you can't find it in your router
ルータに見つからない場合
bring Plex PI up on the screen on this
これでPlex PIを画面に表示します
system so plug a keyboard and mouse and
システムはキーボード とマウス を 接続する
monitor into this turn it on and and
これを監視してオンにして
Ethernet turn it on and then press alt
Ethernetで電源を入れてからaltを押す
f4 once you see Plex that will bring you
あなたが持ってくるプレックスを見たらf4
to the desktop then bring up the
それからデスクトップ に
terminal and type I P space a enter that
端末とタイプIPスペース
will show you the IP address of this
この IPアドレスが表示されます
device look for something like
デバイスはのようなものを探します
192.168.1.0 I address it will say IP
192.168.1.0私はそれがIPを言うだろうアドレス
ipv4 hopefully and hopefully you'll be
うまくいけば、そして うまく いけば、ipv4に なるでしょう
able to attract that
それを 引き付けること ができる
yep let us know okay give us an update
うん 私たち に更新を 与える大丈夫 知らせ
I'd love to hear from you we have a
私は あなたから私 たちが持っているの を聞いてみたいです
question from Carsten says inspired by
Carstenからの質問は
you I've just fought a pi3 installed the
あなたは私が インストールしたpi3を戦った
Plex PI server so far so good
これまでのところプレックスPIサーバはとても良い
however when logging in a notification
ただし、通知にログインすると
appears that an update is now available
アップデート が利用可能になったようです
version one point twelve point zero
バージョン1ポイント12ポイントゼロ
point four eight yes my multi-million
ポイント 4エイトはい私の数百万
dollar question is how do I get to
ドルの質問は私がどのように取得するかです
upgrade my Plex as I have made the lazy
私 は 怠惰 にしたので 私の プレックス を アップグレード
installation hope to hear from you soon
インストールは あなた から すぐ に聞くことを願ってい ます
greetings from Denmark nice thanks
デンマーク 素敵な 感謝の挨拶
Carsten
カルステン
okay so million dollar question does
大丈夫なので百万ドルの質問は
that mean if I answer this - any effort
私がこれに答えるならそれは意味 - どんな努力でも
that I will get a million dollars I hope
私は 私が望む百万ドルを 得るでしょう
so because we would really like that
私たちは本当にそれが好き だから
fiber Internet okay so I think let's see
ファイバー インターネット 大丈夫ですので見てみましょう
so when logging in okay so the the what
だからログインしても大丈夫そう何が
is happening here is that Plex updates
ここで起こっているのはプレックスのアップデートです
their own software and this is really
自分のソフトウェアでこれ は 本当に
something you don't really have to worry
あなたが本当に 心配する必要 はありません何か
about you can ignore that for now
あなたについては今のところそれを無視することができます
because Plex PI is still young okay so
Plex PIはまだ若いので大丈夫なので
remember that Plex PI is version 1.2 at
Plex PIはバージョン1.2です。
the time of this broadcast so I'm doing
この放送の時なので私はやっています
my best to simplify the process one of
私の最高は、プロセスを簡素化するための1 の
the things I will be simplifying Karsten
物事は私が カルステンを 簡素化 さ れます
is the update process some people have
何人かの人々が持っている 更新 プロセスです。
gotten into the terminal and done in a
ターミナルに得とで行われ
disk upgrade and everything else and
ディスクのアップグレードとその他すべて
broken their Plex pie and then emailed
プレックスパイを壊してからメール
me and said why is my Plex by not
私と なぜ私の プレックスがないことで あると述べました
working now I would probably I would
私は、 私は おそらく今 考え でしょう取り組ん
just suggest that for the time being
当分の間それを示唆しなさい
just hang tight because I'm updating it
私は それを 更新していますので、 ちょうど タイトハング
for you I'm doing those updates and then
あなたのために私はそれらの更新をしているそしてそれから
releasing version 1.3 and inevitably
バージョン1.3をリリースし、必然的に
will be releasing software that will
ソフトウェア をリリースする予定です
auto update the system for you so what
オートは あなたのための システムを更新 だから何
it is is that Plex has brought out a new
それはプレックスが新しいものを引き出したということです
version that's the software that we use
バージョンは私達が使用するソフトウェアです
to operate Plex PI and then they've
Plex PIを運用するために
displayed within their interface there's
彼らのインターフェース内に表示されている
an update available well it's a little
利用可能なアップデートそれは少しです
complicated because you can't download
ダウンロードできないので複雑です
that update and install it because Plex
そのアップデートとインストール Plex
Pi is a whole different can of worms
Piはまったく異なる ワームの 缶です
it's built to be an out-of-the-box
すぐ に使えるように 構築され てい ます
experience so it's up to me now to now
経験、それは 今の 今 まで 私 に ありますので、
take that out of the bottom of the box
箱の底 からそれ を 取る
experience and make it so that it
経験し、それができるようにする
auto-update by itself without you having
あなたが持っていなくても自分自身で自動更新
to intervene and without breaking things
物を壊さずに介入する
that's key yes so you can ignore those
それが重要な ので、あなたはそれらを無視することができます
upgrades at the moment and you know I
現時点でアップグレードし、あなた は私 を 知っている
say that only with the stipulation that
という 規定 だけで
I know I'm working to update them for
私はそれらを更新するために働いていることを知っています
you so you don't have to worry about
もしあなたが 心配する必要はありません ので
falling years behind it's not going to
何年も遅れ ているのではない
happen unless I get hit by a bus don't
私はバスに見舞われない限り起こりません
do that I will try my best not to but
私は自分の ベストを 尽くすかということ ではないの が、
your million dollar donation today for
今日のあなたの百万ドルの寄付
my answer so I should make it out okay
私の答えはそう私はそれを大丈夫にする必要があります
and should be able to update that for
そしてそれを更新することができるはずです
you yeah
ええ
but appreciate the question can we
しかし私達にできる質問に感謝
backtrack a little bit to rob Gore sure
ロブ ・ゴア確か に少し 後戻り
okay did I miss something well actually
大丈夫私は実際に何かを逃した
the chat room has helped us out oh yeah
チャットルームは私たちを助けてくれた ああそうそう
you asked does anybody remember when we
あなたが尋ねたのは誰か
covered the last question
最後の質問について
yeah and soul boo souls come to the
うんと魂のブー魂が来る
rescue and said dry episode 407 because
救助と言った ので、ドライエピソード407
you answered the CIFS question on that
あなたはそれに関するCIFSの質問に答えまし た
episode bless okay episode 407 was
エピソードbless 大丈夫エピソード407でした
viewer question extravaganza
視聴者の質問
our viewers have supplied us with a
私たちの視聴者は私たちに
plethora of questions and some great
たくさんの質問といくつかの素晴らしい
comments with topics like NFS and Samba
NFSや Samba などのトピックに対するコメント
CIFS ah Thank You soul boo nice okay
CIFSああありがとう魂のブーいい ね大丈夫
episode 407 Rob Gor there you go so boo
エピソード407 Rob Gorがそこにいる のでブー
and community thank you very much see
そしてコミュニティありがとうございます
who needs to have a search on the
を検索する必要がある人
website when you have a chat room I know
チャットルームがあるときのWebサイト
it's awesome yeah all right do we have
それは素晴らしいですええ、すべての権利、我々が持っています
time for one more question I think you
私は あなたを 考えるもう一つの質問には時間
know we've got news still to cover all
まだすべてを網羅するニュースがあることを知っている
right and so if okay oh yeah I'm so used
正しいそしてそうであれば大丈夫ああそうだ私はとても慣れている
to Sasha doing she's not here so if
彼女がここにいないのであれば サーシャに
you've sent in a question we haven't
あなたは私達が持っていない質問を送りました
been able to cover it yet please no we
まだ 我々が それを してください カバーしていないこと ができました
will come back to you next week and
来週あなたに 戻ってくる と、
please keep the questions coming
質問を続けてください
don't forget t-shirts go to cap 5 dot TV
Tシャツは5ドットテレビをキャップに行くことを忘れないでください
slash shirts I'm gonna say that just
スラッシュシャツ私はそれを言うつもりだよ
leading into the news and it's that
ニュースにつながるとそれはそれです
million dollars I would really
私は本当に万ドル
appreciate that I'll donate 10 points to
に 10ポイント寄付します
charity and and we'll we'll upgrade a
慈善団体と私 たちは アップグレードします
few things around here well find this
ここのまわりのいくつかの事はよくこれを見つける
good will finally pay for that camera
そのカメラの代価はようやく上がるだろう
that B&amp;H has been so good to let us use
B&amp;Hは 私たちが使うこと ができるようにとても 良かった
blessed
祝福された
oh yeah have you guys been enjoying this
そうそう皆さんはこれを楽しんでされています
camera and we really see the difference
カメラと私たちは本当に違いがわかります
when we puts a shellac on the old camera
古いカメラに シェラックを かけたとき
back and forth between the two cameras
2台のカメラ間を行ったり来たり
it's it's amazing so yeah all right you
それはそれは素晴らしいです のでそうそう あなたのすべて
ready to do the news I am ready to do
私がする準備ができているニュースをする準備ができて
right sirs all right here are the
ここにすべての 右の姉妹 は
stories were covering this week in the
物語は この週を カバー し、
categories okay
カテゴリー大丈夫
all right you could have figured it out
あなたはそれを考え出したかもしれないすべての権利
you know where we are oh yeah I know
あなたは私たちがどこにいるか知っている
where we are I have a lot of buttons to
私たちは、 私は 、ボタンの多くを持っているところ
push do you guys see all this stuff in
あなたはみんなでこれらすべてのものを見ますか
front of me now he wants me to start
私の前に今彼は私に始めてほしい
pushing buttons on this I'm used to the
この上の ボタンを押すの は私が慣れている
remote I know you've got rid of the
リモート私はあなたが取り除くのを知っている
remote since I gave up it is alright no
私はそれをあきらめて 以来リモート は 大丈夫です
okay all right here are the stories were
大丈夫 大丈夫 、ここで 話は あり ました
covering this week in the category 5 TV
カテゴリ 5テレビ で今週のカバー
newsroom Elon Musk a man prone to
ニュース編集室イーロン・マスクになりやすい人
ludicrous deadlines has birthed yet
滑稽な締め切りはまだ生まれました
another test flights of his Mars
彼の火星のもう一つのテスト飛行
spaceship next year
来年の宇宙船
a drone owner has been charged as
無人機の所有者はとして請求されています
starting a fire that destroyed 300 acres
300エーカー を 破壊し た火事を始める
of grassland in Arizona's Coconino
アリゾナのココニーノの草原
National Forest a new study shows that
国有林の新しい調査によると、
less than half of ransomware targets who
ランサムウェアの半分 以下が 誰を標的にしているか
pay actually get the files back and
実際に支払う戻ってファイルを取得し、
ransomware for robots is the next big
ロボット用のランサムウェアは次の大きなものです
security nightmare these stories are
セキュリティの悪夢は これらの物語です
coming right up
すぐに来る
don't go anywhere whether you shop on
あなたが買い物をするかどうか、どこにも行かないでください。
think geek gearbest B&amp;H Photo Video eBay
考えるオタクgearbest B＆HフォトビデオのeBay
or Amazon or even if you want a free
またはAmazon、あるいは無料でも欲しいのなら
trial of audible you'll find the best
可聴 の裁判あなたは最高のを見つけることができます
deals and support the shows we produce
私達が作り出すショーを取り引きし、支え なさい
by simply visiting the shopping sites
単にショッピングサイトを訪れることによって
you already frequent by using the links
あなたはすでにリンクを使って頻繁にいます
on our website visit category 5 TV slash
当社のウェブサイト上でカテゴリ 5 テレビスラッシュを ご覧ください
partners for the full and ever-growing
成長し続けている完全なパートナー
list and help us create more free
リストアップして、 より無料で 作成 できる ようにしましょう
content like this show thank you for
この番組のようなコンテンツはありがとうございます
shopping with our partners and thank you
パートナーと買い物をしてありがとう
for watching the
を見て
is the category 5 TV newsroom covering
カテゴリ 5のテレビ ニュースルームのカバーです
the week's top tech stories with a
と今週のトップハイテク物語
slight linux bias
わずかなLinuxバイアス
I'm Jeff Wesson and here are the top
私はJeff Wessonです、そしてここがトップです
stories we're following this week Elon
今週の ストーリー
Musk a man prone to ludicrous deadlines
ばかげた締め切りになりやすい男ムスク
has burst yet birthed yet another idea
バーストしているがまだ生まれている
test flights of his Mars spaceship next
彼の火星宇宙船の次のテスト飛行
year he told the audience at the South
彼 は南の観客 に語った年
by Southwest festival in Austin Texas I
テキサス州オースティンのサウスウェストフェスティバルで
think we'll be able to do short flights
短いフライトができると思います
up and down sometime in the first half
前半のいつか上下に
of next year he put a dark spin on it
来年 、彼はそれに暗いスピンをかけます
though saying that it's vital that
それはそれが不可欠で あると言って も
humans reach the red planet before the
人間は前に赤い惑星に到達します
next world war and saying that a Mars
次の 世界大戦と言って火星だ
colony would reduce the chance of an
コロニーの可能性を低減するであろう
extended new Dark Age if a nuclear
核があれば新しい暗黒時代を延長
conflict were to wipe out life on Earth
対立は地球上の生命を一掃することでした
but we'd rather keep things optimistic
しかし、私たちは 物事を楽観的にし たいのです。
so enough about that after a string of
文字列の後にそれについて十分に
failed rockets and near bankruptcy
失敗したロケットと破産近く
SpaceX wowed the world with this Falcon
SpaceXはこのファルコンで世界を驚かせました
Heavy flight in February a highlights
2月の重飛行ハイライト
reel of the event soundtrack to David
Davidのイベント サウンドトラックのリール
Bowie's life on Mars was shown to
火星でのボウイの生活は、
attendees at the festival the ultimate
祭りの究極の参加者
goal of the mission of course is a Mars
もちろんミッションの目標は火星です
colony at the event musk painted a
イベント時のコロニーのムスク塗装済み完成品
picture of what he felt such a society
彼がそのような 社会 を感じたものの写真
would need to look like in order to be a
になるには、 次のようになる必要があります。
success he said he was excited about the
成功彼は興奮と言いました
potential for launching new industries
新しい産業を立ち上げる可能性
from a completely fresh starting point
完全に新鮮な出発点から
Mars will need pizza joints and one day
火星はピザの関節と一日が必要になります
people will need a Mars bar he said
人々 は 彼が言っ た火星のバー が 必要に なり ます
congratulating congratulating himself on
おめでとうございます
the dad joke regardless of our
お父さん は私たちに 関係なく冗談を言う
individual opinions of Elon Musk the
Elon Musk theの個々の意見
prevailing mood here is that he is a
ここで優勢な気分は彼が
visionary of the highest order and if he
最高次数のビジョナリーであれば
doesn't try to get us to Mars
私達を火星に連れて行こ うとしない
who will I like this idea of going to
誰が私は に 行くの この アイデアを 好き になるでしょう
Mars I do it's it's something that we've
私は 火星 だ
never done I mean we've talked about
やったことがない私たちが話したことを意味
yeah how many things can you say that
ええ、 あなたは何個のことを言うことができます
about I know I mean we've reached a time
私たちは 時間に 達し た という意味
and in our society in our global
そして私達の社会で私達の全体的な
everything where we just I feel like
私たちだけのようなものすべて
we've done everything yeah you know
私たちはあなたが知って いる うん すべてをやった
we're reinventing the wheel on some
我々はいくつかの車輪を再発明している
things but it's but have we got LTE
物事がそれはそれだが私たちはLTEを持っている
internet on the moon no that's next year
来月の月のインターネット
ok yeah but I mean the question for this
ええ OK 私は 、このための質問を 意味します
one becomes is it going to take the six
一つになるのは6つ を 取る つもりです
months to get there is Elon gonna have
そこに着く数ヶ月はエロンが持っているつもりです
some
一部
faster process for forgetting to Mars
火星を忘れるためのより速いプロセス
yeah you know I know he's been working
ええ、あなたは私が彼が 働いていた ことを知っている知って いる
tirelessly with at building new forms of
の新しい形を構築することに精力的に
propulsion yes and things like this so
推進力はいそして こんな こと
where that's gonna take us I guess next
それが私たちを連れて行くつもり私は次に思います
year we'll know when he starts the test
彼がテストを開始した年がわかります
flights I guess that's when we're gonna
それは私たちが行くつもりだ時だと思う
really know what they've accomplished so
彼らが達成したことを本当に知っている
far right and I mean with the payload
一番右で、ペイロードとは
size that the that his Falcon heavy X I
その彼のファルコン ヘビー XI というサイズ
think that was called has won't be
呼ばれたとは思わない
enough to set up a full colony so you're
フルコロニーを設定するのに十分なので
gonna have to probably send me multiple
おそらく私に複数送信する必要があります
you know flights ever think yeah plus
あなたはフライト が ええプラス だと思う今まで 知っている
SpaceX has reduced the cost of space
SpaceXはスペースのコストを削減しました
travel
旅行
absolutely so another goal is an
絶対に別の目標 は
exploration multiple flights at the same
探査複数のフライトを同時に
time and hey here's our people pod and
時間とこんにちはここで私たちの人々はポッドです
here's all of our right I mean who knows
これが私たちのすべて の権利 です。
you know what they'd have to have
あなたは彼らが持っているべきことを知っています
fail-safes in place that you know each
あなたがそれぞれ知っている場所にフェイルセーフ
ship would have a certain number of
船には一定数の
people a certain number of supplies
一定数 の物資
mm-hmm so that if one didn't make it
mm-hmmなので、できなかった場合は
that people who did make it aren't
それを 作った人々 はそうではない
without water for all sampler as long as
限り、 すべての サンプラー 用の水なし
you've got Matt Damon to poop on
Matt Damonにうんざりさせる
potatoes you're alright is that real
あなたが大丈夫じゃがいもそれは本当です
life well that's what happened in the
人生はよくそれが起こったのです
movie okay but scientists have said that
映画は大丈夫だが科学者は 言っ た
that is probably the most realistic way
それがおそらく 最も 現実的な方法です
of actually getting potatoes to grow on
じゃがいもを 実際 に育てる
Mars Wow yeah interesting Jeff I know
火星うわあ 私が知っている 面白い ジェフ
you just kind of threw that in there
あなたはちょっとそこにそれを投げました
folks if you were wondering pooping on
人々は あなたが思って 上pooping れた場合
potatoes is the way to go wonderful okay
ジャガイモは大丈夫素晴らしい移動するための方法であります
a drone owner has been charged with
無人機の所有者が 課金 さ れています
starting a fire that destroyed 300 acres
300エーカー を破壊した火事を始める
of grassland in a National Forest in
の国有林の草原の
Arizona a drone reportedly caught on
アリゾナ州の無人機が逮捕された
fire after it crashed denting dried
それが 乾燥 したへこみをクラッシュさ せた後に火
grasses in an area called Kendrick Park
Kendrick Parkという地域の草
near Flagstaff about 30 firefighters
フラッグスタッフ近く 約30人の消防士
were able to bring the blaze under
炎を下 に持ち込むことができた
control within a day now if found guilty
有罪であることが判明した場合は今1日以内にコントロール
the drones owner could face a fine
無人偵察機の所有者は 罰金に 直面 する 可能性が あります
community service or even a jail
コミュニティサービスあるいは 刑務所
sentence while tackling the incident
事件に取り組みながら文
last week firefighters preemptively set
先週消防士が先制的に設定
light to the grasslands surrounding a
周辺の草原への光
local landmark the Chapel of the Holy
地元のランドマーク聖礼拝堂
dove to ensure that the small church was
小さな教会が
not
ではない
by the flames warnings were issued to
炎の警告によって警告が出された
drivers in the area as dense smoke from
から密な煙として地域の ドライバー
the fire made driving conditions
火は運転条件を作りました
difficult on roads through the Kendrick
Kendrickを 通る道路では難しい
Park region now while it is legal to fly
それは飛ぶことが合法である間今公園地域
a drone in the US National Forest there
アメリカ国有林の無人機
are strict regulations governing when
を 管理する 厳格な 規制です。
and where they can be flown drones must
そして彼らはどこに飛ぶことができる
not be flown in wilderness areas nor
荒野に飛んではいけません
over areas where wildfires are active in
山火事が活発な地域で
2017 helicopters helping to tackle fire
火事に取り組むのを助けている2017年のヘリコプター
in the very same forest were hampered by
非常に同じフォレストにによって妨げられました。
a drone taking pictures of the blaze now
今炎の写真を撮るドローン
the pilot of that unmanned craft was not
その無人機のパイロットは
identified and firefighting planes and
識別された消防飛行機
helicopters helping to tackle seasonal
季節に取り組むのを助けるヘリコプター
fires in other regions have also been
他の地域 での火災にもなっています
temporarily grounded for fear of a
の恐れのために一時的に接地された
collision with a drone it's unfortunate
ドローンとの衝突は残念です
that recreational drone use has come to
レクリエーションドローンの使用は、
this level where people are not aware
人々が 気づいて いない 、このレベル
that they're actually hampering you know
彼らは実際にあなたが知っていることを妨げていること
emergency situations
緊急事態
oh yeah like be smart if you're gonna
ああそうだあなたがするつもりなら賢いことが好き
fly a drone if they're I mean I get sure
もし彼らがドローンを飛ばすなら私は確実だ
it's great cool footage to film a forest
森を撮影するのは素晴らしいクールな映像です
fire but if you're preventing people
火が、 人々を防げば
from being able to put out that fire
その 火 を消すことができることから
that's not cool
それは、いけてないねえ
or if you're creating the fire well that
またはあなたがよく火を作成している場合に
too no I mean in the case of this drone
あまりにも私 はこのドローンの 場合に は 意味
flier it's not like he intended to crash
それは彼 がクラッシュ するつもりだっ た ようなものではありません
and make it burn so should we be setting
そしてそれを燃やすようにしなさい
up like a drone insurance industry well
ドローン保険業界のように
I think that so if we back up and think
バックアップして 考えれ ば そう思います
about and I don't know the whole you
について、私はあなた全体を知りません
know the details about who this flier
誰がこのチラシについての詳細を知っています
was but first of all his drone caught on
彼の無人機が捕まったのはまず
fire so that tells me it's probably
それはおそらくそれが私に言うように火
gas-propelled right I would expect it's
ガス推進の権利
not a battery-powered drone no and if
ないバッテリ駆動ドローンがない とあれば
that's the case then this is a
それが 事実であり 、これはです
commercial flier like this is not
この ような商業チラシ はそうではありません
somebody that's just a hobbyist like me
誰かが私のようなただの趣味人です
with his electric drones that right you
彼のエレクトリックドローンであなたにぴったりの
know I'm flying around over the trees
木の上を 飛んでいるのを知っている
and safely bringing them down and if
かつ安全に ダウン している場合 、それらを もたらします
they crash they get stuck in the
彼らはクラッシュします
branches and I cry because I just lost
私はちょうど失ったので枝と私は泣く
$600 in drone hardware right that's how
ドローンハードウェアで $ 600 正しい
it goes for me but so we must have they
それは私のために行くが、だから我々は彼らを持っている必要があります
must be a consumer flyer
消費者フライヤーでなければならない
commercial flyer or be serious enough
商業チラシまたは 十分に真剣である
about it that he's using it for
それについて 、彼はそれを使っていること
commercial purposes I would expect like
私が 期待する商業目的
unless you're just filthy stinking rich
あなたが不潔な臭いだけではない限り
and you own a really big expensive
そしてあなたは本当に大きな高価なものを所有しています
gas-powered drone not anymore but there
ガソリンドローンは もうあり ませ ん
are regulations and there are laws that
規制であり、法律があります
say that if you were flying commercially
あなたが商業的に飛んでいたと言う
there are rules and yes you have to be
ルールがあり、そうでなけれ ば なりません
insured okay so if he was flying if he
彼ならば、彼が飛んでいたので、もし大丈夫 被保険者
was flying without insurance that's an F
保険なしで飛んでいたのはF
because I don't know then you know who
私は知らないのであなたは誰 を 知っ ているから
is liable for that who pays for that who
その人に支払う人には責任がある
pays for the damage yeah that's the
損傷のために支払うええ、それはです
question it'll be very interesting to
それは非常に面白いだろう質問
see how that one plays out anymore I'd
私はもう 1つが出て再生する 方法 だろう 見ます
like to know more about who he is why
彼が誰なのかについてもっと知りたい
obviously they they found him yes so he
明らかに 彼らは彼ら が イエス を 見つけた ので彼は
fessed up because the you know the other
あなたは他の人を知っているので怒って
person who was flying a drone and
無人機を飛行していた人
hampering emergency services they never
彼らは決してしない緊急サービスを妨げる
found them right because a drone can be
無人機がすることができる ので 、それらを正しく見つけました
kilometres away and again these are
何キロも離れて
these are not your average consumer
これらはあなたの平均的な消費者ではありません
drones these is right these are big
無人偵察機これらは正しいこれらは大きい
heavy drones that can be flown from
から 飛ぶことができるヘビードローン
kilometres away using 3d goggles and
3Dゴーグル を 使って キロメートル
virtual reality yes yeah that's true
バーチャルリアリティそうそうです
nobody interested see how that one
興味がある人は誰でも
shapes out mm-hmm all right in a
で MM-HMM すべての権利を 形作ります
shocking revelation criminals proved to
衝撃的な啓示犯が証明した
be untrustworthy Oh a new study shows
新しい研究ショー ああ信頼できません
that less than half of ransomware
ランサムウェアの半分以下
targets who pay up actually get their
実際に支払いをするターゲットは
files back paying off ransomware a
ランサムウェアを返済するファイル
demand is a great way to end up losing
需要は失うことになる素晴らしい方法です
both your money and your files this
あなたのお金とファイルの両方
according to a study from security
セキュリティからの研究に よる と
company cyber edge which found that
それを見つけた会社のサイバーエッジ
those hit by ransomware infection the
ランサムウェアに感染した人
best bet is probably to just restore
最善の策は、おそらく単に復元することです
from a backup the survey based on a poll
バックアップに基づいて、アンケートに基づく調査
of information security professionals
情報セキュリティの 専門家
found that less than half of those who
半数以下の人が
pay a ransom end up getting their data
身代金を払っ てデータを入手する
back the report says that 55% of people
報告に戻ると、 55％ の 人が、
who surveyed reported a malware
調査対象者はマルウェアを報告しました
infection hitting their systems in 2017
2017年に感染したシステム
Spain had the highest rate with 80% of
スペインは80％の最高率を持っていた
respondents malware followed by
マルウェアの後に続いた
companies in China at 74% and Mexico at
中国の企業は 74％、メキシコの企業は
70 1.9 percent in the u.s. 50 3.8
私たちの 70 1.9 パーセント 50 3.8
percent of respondents were hit by
回答者の割合は
ransomware
ランサムウェア
slightly under half of those in the UK
英国の人口の半分以下
49.5% were hit
49.5％がヒットしました
overall seventy two point four percent
全体の72ポイント4パーセント
of those who were infected with
に感染した人々のうち
ransomware were able to get their data
ランサムウェアはデータを入手することができました
back
バック
most of those however were companies
しかしそれらのほとんどは会社でした
that simply ignored the ransom demands
身代金要求を単に無視した
and restored their systems with
そして彼らのシステムを
uninfected backup copies the study found
感染していないバックアップには調査結果が見つかりました
that eighty six point nine percent of
その86 パーセントの9パーセント
those who refused to pay the demand
要求 を払うこと を拒んだ人たち
ended up recovering their data of those
それらの彼らのデータ を 回復すること になった
who cave to the demand and paid the
誰が要求に応えて
ransom forty nine point four percent
身代金49ポイント4 パーセント
said they did recover their data well
彼らは彼らのデータを うまく 回復したと言った
50.6% ended up losing it anyway
50.6％ が とにかく 負け た
the nutshell shocking conclusion is that
一言で言えば衝撃的な結論はそれです
criminals don't always stay true to
犯罪者は常に真滞在していません。
their work good to hear that so many
そんなに多くの ことを聞いて 彼らの 仕事は良い
folks have reliable disconnected backups
人々 は信頼できる切断されたバックアップを持っています
yes this is one of the fears with and
はいこれはとの恐怖の一つです
the dangers with ransomware is that it
ランサムウェアの危険性はそれです。
doesn't just encrypt the files on your
自分のファイルを暗号化するだけで はありません
server and your computer's it encrypts
サーバーと あなたのコンピューターの暗号化
the files on your backup that's right so
右それでは 、バックアップ のファイル
what happens if you don't have a backup
バックアップがないとどうなりますか
and you don't pay the ransom is there a
そして 、あなたは そこに ある身代金を払っていません
third option or you don't have a backup
3番目の選択肢、 または バックアップがない
you pay the ransom as a last ditch
あなたは最後の溝として身代金を支払う
effort and they don't come through yeah
努力と彼らは そうで はありません
like is there another way to get this
これを取得する別の方法があるように
data back that is a really you know my
データバック それはあなたが 私の 知っ て いる本当にです
answer to that would be very iffy okay
それへの答えは大丈夫大丈夫 だろう
b-but you might be surprised to know
b-しかしあなたは 知って 驚いた かもしれませ ん
that my answer would be maybe okay
私の 答えは多分 大丈夫 だろうということ
perhaps perhaps there's each other
おそらくお互いがいる
option because what happens with these
何が起こるのか
with these types of things ransomware
これらの種類のものを使って
and and and things the there are often
そして、そして、そしてそこにあるもの
master keys these are keys that the
マスターキーは、 これらのキーです
hackers create in order to be able to
ハッカーのことができるようにするために作成します
recover the files and once those master
ファイルを回復し、 それらのマスターになったら
keys are deciphered by security
鍵はセキュリティによって解読されます
engineers tools are released that help
エンジニアのツールがリリースされました
people to recover their files using the
人々が使用してファイルを回復 するには
master key okay so ESET is one of those
マスターキーは大丈夫ですのでESETはそのうちの一つです
companies that has worked really hard to
本当に一生懸命働いた会社
release tools to decrypt files and there
ファイルを復号化するためのツールをリリースし、そこに
are there are actually a number of
実際にはいくつもありますか
security research companies security
セキュリティ研究会社セキュリティ
like
好き
anti-malware companies that have worked
働いているマルウェア対策会社
together to create repositories of their
一緒にリポジトリを作成する
tools so that people who are infected
感染している人々のためのツール
with particular types of ransomware
特定の種類 のランサムウェア
infections can recover their files right
感染は自分のファイルを正しく回復することができます
so again it's not a guaranteed you're
だから、それはあなたが保証されていません
going to get your data back if you run
実行したらデータを取り戻す
this free program it doesn't work that
この無料プログラムではうまくいきません
way but to know that there are people
人 がいることを知るための 方法
and companies out there that are working
そしてそこ に働いている会社
hard to combat this issue is a really
この問題に対処するのは難しい 実際に あります
encouraging thing and I'll actually show
励ましの事と私は実際に見せてあげる
you the website it's I believe it was no
もし それが 、私はそれがありませんでしたと信じてい ますウェブサイト
more ransom dot-org
もっと身代金ドットオルガン
no more ransom dot-org no more ransom or
これ以上身代金はありませんdot-org これ以上 身代金はあり ません または
I must have mistyped it but it
私はそれを誤入力したにちがいないが
redirected anyways so here we are no
とにかくリダイレ​​クトされた ので、 ここで私たちはいない
more ransom org and you see that there
もっと身代金組織とあなたはそこにいることがわかります
are a ton of folks that are involved in
関係し て いる たくさんの人たちです
this you've got you know the main
これであなたは主を知っています
associate partners
準パートナー
BitDefender Trend Micro is a big
BitDefender Trend Microは大きいです
contributor vast we've got law
私たちは法律を持っている 広大な寄稿
enforcement agencies that work with them
彼らと協力する執行機関
other partners which is where we find
私たちが見つけるところである他のパートナー
ESET for example who've contributed some
例えばESETはいくつかの貢献をしました
code and they also distribute their own
コードと彼らも 自分自身を配布します
tools so here's what we do
ツールなので、ここで私たちは何をすべきか
so decryption tools now there's other
復号化ツールには他にもあります
great information here so check it out
ここに素晴らしい情報があるのでそれをチェックしてください
but go into decryption tools and you can
復号化ツールを使用すれば、
find all these different ransomware
これらすべての 異なるランサムウェアを 見つける
decrypt errs right so these are all
正しく復号化されるので、これら すべて
ransom ransomware viruses or malware so
身代金ランサムウェアウイルスやマルウェア そう
if I'm for example infected with the
例えば私が
crisis ransomware there are two tools
2つのツールがあります
one of them from Kaspersky Lab and one
そのうちの1つはKaspersky Labから、もう1つは
of them from Trend Micro and these two
トレンドマイクロ とこれら2つ
tools are designed specifically to
ツールは特別に設計されています
decrypt the files that are encrypted
暗号化されているファイルを復号化する
using that particular malware oh so if
ああ そうであれば 、その特定のマルウェアを使用して
you're fortunate yeah there may be a way
あなたは幸運だそうな方法があるかもしれません
to recover those files even if you don't
あなたがいない場合でも、これらのファイルを回復する
have a backup and even if you don't have
バックアップを持っていて、持っていなくても
if you haven't been able to recover them
あなたがそれらを回復することができなかったならば
by paying the ransom but that is not a
身代金を支払うことによってしかしそれはではありません
fail-safe that is not a reason to not
フェイルセーフ はそれが理由では ない
protect yourself that is a last-ditch
最後の溝である自分自身を守る
effort of security engineers to help you
あなたを助けるためのセキュリティエンジニアの努力
the fact is you need to have a good
事実はあなたが 善 を 持っている 必要があるということです
backup you have to have a backup that is
バックアップする必要があるバックアップが必要 です
disconnected from anything that this
これというもの から切り離された
kind of infection can touch so
感染の種類はそう触れることができます
air-gapped unplugged taken home rotated
エアギャップのプラグを抜いて家に持ち帰って回転
every week and never touching the
毎週そして決して触れないで
network while ransomware is a thing yes
ネットワークランサムウェアは イエス のものである一方、
okay researchers have found that they
大丈夫な研究者は 彼らがそれを見つけた
were able to infect robots with
ロボットに感染することができた
ransomware in the real world such
そのような 現実の 世界 でのランサムウェア
attacks would be highly damaging to
攻撃は、非常にダメージを与える だろう
businesses if robotics security isn't
ロボティクスセキュリティではない
addressed ransomware has long been a
アドレス付きランサムウェアは長い間
headache for PC and smartphone users but
PCとスマートフォンユーザーにとって頭痛
in the future it could be robots that
将来ロボットに なる かも
stopped working unless a ransom is paid
身代金が支払われ ない限り 仕事をやめ た
researchers at the security company
警備会社の 研究者
ioactive have shown how they managed to
ioactive は彼らがどうやって管理したかを示しました
hack the humanoid NAO robot by Softbank
Softbankの ヒューマノイド NAOロボットを ハッキング
and infected one with custom-built
そして カスタムメイドで 感染したもの
ransomware the researchers said the same
ランサムウェア、研究者らは同じと述べた
attack would work on the pepper robot as
攻撃はペッパーロボットに
well after the infection the robot has
ロボットが感染した後も
shown insulting the its audience and
観客を侮辱する
demanding to be fed Bitcoin
ビットコインの供給を要求
cryptocurrency in order to restore
復元するための暗号通貨
systems back to normal
システムを通常に戻す
now while a tiny robot making threats
小さなロボットが脅威になる
might initially sound amusing if a
最初のうちは面白そうに聞こえないかもしれません。
little bit creepy the proof-of-concept
概念実証が少し不気味
attack demonstrates the risks associated
攻撃は関連するリスクを実証する
with lack of security and robots and how
セキュリティやロボットが不足している
organizations that employ robots could
ロボットを使う組織は
suddenly see parts of their business
突然彼らのビジネスの一部を見る
grind to a halt should they become a
彼らがになったら停止するために挽く
victim of ransomware Caesar sir Otto CTO
ランサムウェアの被害者Caesar sir Otto CTO
at IO in active labs said in order to
IOで活性ラボに する ために、前記
get a business ownership to pay a ransom
身代金を支払う ために事業の 所有権を 取得する
to a hacker you could make robots stop
ハッカーにロボットを 止めさせる
working and because the robots are
作業ロボットである ため 、
directly tied to production and services
生産とサービスに直結
when they stop working they'll cause a
彼らが働かなくなると、彼らは
financial problem for the owner losing
所有者を 失う ための経済的問題
money every second that they're not
彼らはそうではないと 毎秒お金
working now taking what was learned in
で 学んだ ことを取って今働く
previous studies into security
セキュリティに関するこれまでの研究
vulnerabilities of robots researchers
ロボット 研究者の脆弱性
were able to inject the right code in
正しいコードを挿入することができました。
pepper and nao robots to make to take
取るために作るコショウとnaoロボット
complete control of the systems giving
システムの完全制御
them the option to shut the robot down
ロボット を シャットダウン するオプション
or
または
by its actions the researchers said it
その行動によって研究者はそれを言った
was possible for an attacker with access
攻撃者はアクセス権を持っ て いる可能性が あります。
to the Wi-Fi network the robot is
ロボットはWi-Fiネットワークに
running on to infect malicious code in
悪意のあるコードに感染するために実行している
into the machine unlike computers robots
コンピュータロボットとは異なり、マシンに
don't yet store vast amounts of
まだ大量のものを保管していない
vulnerable information that the user
脆弱な情報であること
might be willing to pay a ransom to
に身代金を支払っても構わないと思っている
retrieve but as companies often don't
企業の場合はそうではないが
use backups to resource systems from if
ifからリソースシステムへのバックアップを使用する
a robot becomes infected with ransomware
ロボットがランサムウェアに感染する
it's also impossible for the user to
それは への ユーザーのためにも不可能です
restore it to normal by themselves so if
そうならば自分でそれを正常に復元する
we have the ability to have our robots
私たちはロボットを持つことができます
hacked you knew it was coming guys you
あなたはそれがみんなに あなたを 来ていた知っていたハッキング
knew it was coming would it be done in
それがやってくることを知っていた
the same way that they could be hacking
彼らが ハッキング する可能性があるのと同じ方法
autonomous cars hmm like you know I'm
あなたが知っているような 自律走行車 うーん
thinking of Wi-Fi exploits and yeah you
あなたは、Wi-Fi悪用を考えてとええ
know what I'm obviously you know going
私は明らかにあなたが行くことを知っているものを知っている
to the Hollywood side of things I'm
私は物事のハリウッド側に
thinking of the movie I Robot where
どこ の映画Iロボットのことを考え
you've got one mainframe that's running
実行中のメインフレームが1つあります。
all the computers if somebody found a
誰かが見つけた場合は、すべてのコンピュータ
way to hack right you know like I think
私が思うように あなたが知って いる 権利 をハックする方法
I think it was peppers running in a
私はそれがで実行されているピーマンだったと思います
hospital there's a pepper
病院コショウが あります
yeah yeah you know could somebody hack
誰かがハック可能性ええ、ええ 、あなたは知っています
that to hurt people potentially yeah I
人を傷つけるためにそうだね
guess you know right I mean
あなたが 正しいことを知って いる と思います
theoretically they could and but you
理論的には可能ですがあなたは
know they they're kind of the story says
彼らは彼らが物語の一種であると知っている
that you know your dad is not a problem
あなたのお父さんは問題ではないことを知っていること
but any device on your network is an
しかし、 あなたのネットワーク上のどのデバイスも
entry point for attack right so if a
攻撃のエントリポイント右 もしそうであれば
robot were an entry point for an attack
ロボットは 攻撃の 入り口 でした
and now that robot is infected that
そして今、そのロボットはそれに感染している
robots on the same Wi-Fi as your server
サーバー と同じWi-Fi上のロボット
mm-hmm and now all of a sudden the robot
mm-hmmそして 今や 突然のロボット
can use the code to go out into the
出て行くために 、コードを使用することができます
server and start encrypting files there
サーバーとそこにファイルの暗号化を開始
right I mean I'm thinking of production
正しい私は生産を考えているということです
companies you know so literally so many
文字通りとてもたくさんの あなたが知って いる 会社
on industries yeah they use robotics and
産業界ではロボットを使っ ている
I mean if somebody hacked in there and
誰かがそこに侵入したとしたら
say shut out an entire facility oh yeah
施設全体を閉鎖すると言う
I mean imagine that the productivity and
生産性 と
the financial impact of shutting down an
シャットダウンの財務的影響
automaker for one day even or you could
でも、一日のために自動車メーカーや あなたは可能性があり
take it one dark step further and look
さらに一歩進んで見て
at military right right because military
軍事的に正しいから
is work
仕事です
toward using robots more and more to
ロボットをもっと使う
carry heavy artillery and carry even the
重砲を運び、
you know this the just essentials and
あなたはこれだけの必需品を知っています
things like that so you know what would
その ようなものなので、あなたは何ができるか知っている
happen if their network of robots were
ロボットのネットワークが
debilitated by ransomware during during
中にランサムウェアによって衰弱した
like during a war or something so what
戦争中か何かのように
you're saying is that to bring this news
あなたが言っているのは 、 このニュース を持ってくる ということです
to full loop we go back to you on musk
完全なループに私たちは ムスクで あなたに戻ります
and we should just set up on Mars colony
そして私達は火星の植民地にセットアップするべきです
it might be the next it may be necessary
それは次に 必要 かもしれません
I know what are your thoughts folks I
私は あなたの思考の 人々 、私が 何を知っています
mean what what risks are there and is
リスクとは何か
there something that needs to be done I
そこで行われる必要があるものを I
think the answer is clearly yes
答えは明らかにイエスだと思う
if these robots can be exploited in this
これらのロボットがこれ で 悪用される可能性がある場合
way I can't imagine that more security
私はそれ 以上のセキュリティを 想像することはできません方法
has not like I'm a little blown away
私は少し吹き飛ばされて好きではない
right now that pepper is vulnerable to
今コショウ はに弱いです
ransomware I how is this possible does
ランサムウェア私 はこれがどのように可能 です か
she run Windows well you know it's it is
彼女はよくあなたはそれがあることを知っているWindowsを実行します
a great point because I mean we use
私たちが使うという意味で素晴らしい点
robotics to assist us on a daily basis
毎日私たちを支援するロボット工学
and if you don't think about these
あなたがこれらについて考えていないなら
things it does become a problem and you
それが問題になること とあなたは
know with pepper being in a hospital
ペッパーが病院にいることを知っている
there is the potential for storing data
データを格納する 可能性が あります
of you know somebody walks in or
誰かが入ってくるのを知っていますか
stealing data well exactly yeah so you
正確にデータを盗む
know somebody walks in they talk to the
誰かが歩くのを知っている
robot say here my symptoms and pepper
ロボットはここに私の症状とコショウを言う
does a quick triage and send you over
簡単なトリアージをしてあなたに送ってください
here send you over there you know if
ここにあなたが知っている場合は あそこに送ります
that's what it turns into
それはそれがになるものです
but all of that information is stored
しかし、 その情報はすべて保存されています
somewhere and then because it would have
どこかにしてから
to then go to patient files you do have
それから あなたが 持っている 患者ファイルに行きます
a storage issue and a connection there's
ストレージの問題と接続があります
a connection obviously to the central
明らかに 中心部 へ の接続
database yeah so I mean there's a lot of
データベースええだから私はたくさんあることを意味
potential problems that come with this
これに 伴う潜在的な問題
and I would hope that developers of
そして私は その開発者が
these robots are thinking about security
これらのロボットはセキュリティを考えています
minded you know protections rather than
保護を知っているのではなく
just hey look at these cool things we
ちょっとちょっとこれらの クールなもの を見てください
can do yeah like I'm thinking of that
ええ行うことができますように、私は そのことを 考えています
about two weeks ago I think there's a
約2 週間 前、私は ある と思います
YouTube video of a robotic dog that
ロボット犬の YouTubeビデオ
opens doors
ドアを開ける
yeah mazing yeah which is cool but what
うん、すごい涼しいがうん
if that dog got hacked and it was
あの犬がハッキングされて
to pick locks and open doors now
鍵を開けてドアを開ける
suddenly you've got a robot for all you
突然あなたの ため の ロボットを 手に入れました
would just build a big strong robot that
それだけで大きな強力なロボットを構築するだろう
just bashes doors down okay so Robocop I
Robocop Iなので、ドアを破壊するだけで構いません。
think my concern is that more care
私の心配は もっと気にする ことだと思う
hasn't been spent on the security thing
セキュリティのことに費やされていない
and we saw the same thing with
と同じことを見た
automobiles yes with hackable systems
ハッキング可能なシステムがある自動車
how can we be bringing out technologies
どのように我々は技術を引き出すことができますか
without understanding the underlining
下線を理解せずに
security how can that not be our
セキュリティどのようにそれは私たちではないことができます
priority to make sure that hey if I'm
私の場合は、こんにちは ことを 確認 する ための優先順位
bringing out robots that are Wi-Fi
Wi-Fiであるロボットを引き出す
connected or we've heard about Bluetooth
接続されているか、 Bluetoothについて聞いたことがある
children's toys that can be hacked and
ハッキング することができます子供のおもちゃ と
compromised yeah from you know the the
あなた からの妥協はい
house next door and and you know these
隣の家と、あなたは これらを 知っています
are concerns children's like baby
子供の赤ちゃんのような関心事です
monitors yes being hacked because when
はい、ハッキングされている かを監視します。
we built this device we fought only
私達は私達が戦ったこの装置を造った
about the video quality and the stream
ビデオ品質とストリームについて
and did not put any work into the
に何の仕事も入れなかった
security how is that possible there
セキュリティはどのように可能ですか
needs to be some kind of yeah I hate to
私が嫌いななんらかの種類である必要があります
say regulations no I don't want to say
規則を言う いいえ私は言いたくない
that but who there needs to be
それが誰である必要があります
accountability absolutely I think is is
アカウンタビリティ絶対に 私が されている と思います
what it boils down to hmm a lot of
それは、多くの HMMするために沸く何
things to think about comment below let
以下のコメント について考えること
us know what you think that's right
私たちはあなたが正しいと思うものを知っています
big thanks to Roy W Nash the Albuquerque
Roy W Nash the Albuquerqueに感謝します
turkey and our community of yours for
七面鳥とあなたのコミュニティ のための
submitting stories to us this week
今週私たちにストーリーを投稿する
thanks for watching the category-five
カテゴリー5を見てくれてありがとう
dot TV newsroom don't forget to Like and
dot TVのニュースルームで は 、「いいね」を忘れ ないで ください。
subscribe for all your tech news with a
であなたのすべての技術ニュースを購読する
slight Linux bias and for more free
ちょっとしたLinuxバイアスともっと 無料
content be sure to check out our website
コンテンツは必ず 当社の ウェブサイト をチェックして ください
from the category-five TV newsroom I'm
私はカテゴリ5のテレビニュース編集室から
Jeff Weston Jeff thank you so much this
Jeff Weston Jeff、ありがとうございます。
is category five technology TV I hope
カテゴリー5テクノロジーテレビです
that you've enjoyed yourself tonight as
あなたは自分自身 として 今夜は楽しんできたこと
we have celebrated Pi Day in the only
私たちは唯一のパイデイを祝い ました
way that we know how which is to talk
私たち がどのように話し て いるか知っている方法
non-stop incessantly for one hour about
約1時間絶え間なく止まる
raspberry pi it's true
ラズベリーパイ
I almost feel bad that I didn't bring
持参しなかったことはほとんど気分が悪くなります
like a raspberry pie to eat on the show
ラズベリーパイのようにショーで食べる
I just would have been a nice you know
私は ちょうど あなたが 知っ て いるよかったよ
focal point speaking of didn't bring you
焦点と言えばあなたを連れてこなかった
have a new raspberry pie that you've
新しいラズベリーパイを食べ た
been working on yes
はい取り組んできました
okay so there's time for more pie folks
大丈夫なので、もっとパイの人々のための時間がある
there's there's always time for pie he's
彼がいるパイはいつでもあります
all
すべて
so leading into Christmas I was looking
私は探していたのでクリスマスにつながる
at getting another Raspberry Pi yeah for
以下のために そう 別のラズベリー パイを 取得で
the purpose of creating a I was going to
私がしようとしていたを作成する目的
do another retropie gaming system nice
素敵な別のretropieゲームシステムを行います
that way you can only you can never have
そのようにすることができますあなただけが持つことはできません
well we've got only the one TV so I was
テレビは1台しかないので、私は
gonna put it on the other TV so that you
あなたがする ように他のテレビにそれ を置くつもりです
know
知っている
yeah it's can play on both you know ho
ええそれはあなたがホを知っている両方で遊ぶことができます
yeah I don't want to play Barry oh I
うん私は バリーああ私 を 再生し たく ない
want to play you know whatever so I was
私がそうであったように あなた が何でも知っているあなた が 遊びたいです
gonna do it for that and then because
そのためにそれをやるつもりだし
it's a headless but I was gonna be
それはヘッドレスですが、 私はするつもりでした
setting up for a headless system
ヘッドレスシステムの設定
potentially but I'm like okay what if I
潜在的にしかし私は私が何をしても大丈夫のようなものです
want to be able to access it and for
それにアクセスできるようにしたいとのために
whatever reason I can't get it to
私がそれを得ることができないどんな理由でも
connect to my TV for visual purposes and
視覚的な目的で 私の テレビに接続する
this has happened with my other PI
これは私の他の PI と一緒に起こった
because yeah I have an off name-brand tv
ええ、 私はオフ ネームブランドのテレビ を持っているので
downstairs I opened up for I think it
階下に開いた
was a 50-inch for like 98 bucks or
98ドルのような50インチだった
something yeah some special sale and
何か 特別なセール
every once in a while the video feed
ビデオフィードは時々刻々
does not work from the PI to the
PIからに動作しません
computer and so to the TV so I wanted to
私はしたいと思ったので、コンピュータとテレビに
get a case that had a an LCD screen or
液晶画面を持っていたケースを取得する
LED I believe screen okay and so the
LED私は大丈夫 と画面を信じているので
case I picked up was I think 25 30 bucks
私が拾ったケースは25 30ドルだと思いました
on Amazon oh I gotta check this out I
アマゾンで私はこれをチェックアウトしなければならない
don't recall the name of it but it was a
それの名前を 思い出す が 、それはなかったん
PI case with a screen I just did a
私はちょうどした画面でPIケース
search for AI case right then the first
AIの 場合を検索する
one because I didn't literally pie case
私は文字通りパイケースではなかった ので一つ
screen yet that's the one I got right
スクリーンはまだ私が得たものです
there that's it a 3.52 that yeah now it
そこにそれは ええ、今で 3.52 それ です
was on sale going into Christmas I think
クリスマスに入って発売中だったと思います
I paid 25 bucks for it
25ドル払った
on exam oh I'm fine but it works really
私は元気です が、それは 実際 に動作し ます
well simple to set up so it pulls the
それは引っ張るようにセットアップするのも簡単
video from GPIO that's correct
GPIOからのビデオは正しい
so you still can plug in to the TV so
あなたはまだテレビにプラグインすることができますので、
same yeah it is effectively a mini
同じええ、それ は事実上 ミニです
desktop so no I mean it doesn't work it
デスクトップはありません ので 、私はそれを 動作 しません意味します
doesn't work out of box you need to
あなた が する 必要 がある箱から出して動作しません
install the drivers on Shuai yeah yeah
ええええ 元帥に ドライバをインストールします
but it was great to work with and it
しかし、それは一緒に仕事をするのは素晴らしかったです
does cause it a mirror image of what you
それ は あなた のものの 鏡像 になり ますか
see on the TV yeah okay yeah cool and
テレビで見てね
it's got a style I mean it's it's a
それはそれはだだ 私が意味するスタイルを持っています
small screen yeah we're talking the size
小さいスクリーンそうそう私達は サイズを話しています
of a pie yeah but it does come with a
パイのええ、それは付属していません
stylus because I've got big meaty
私は大きな肉を持っている のでスタイラス
fingers and the stylus makes it easy to
指とスタイラスで簡単に
move around so I can operate them
私は それを動作させる ことができるように 動き回ります
new system without any issue it's it's
それは それはだ だすべての問題のない新しいシステム
beautiful so if you do have a headless
あなたが頭のない人がいる場合はとても美しい
PI and you're going hey sometimes I
PIとあなたはちょっとちょっと 私になってるよ
can't connect to I can't figure what's
私は何を把握することはできません に接続することはできません
going on whatever this is a great option
これが 素晴らしいオプションであるものは何でも続けます
because you've got you guys these my
あなたはこれらの 私の 人たちを持っている ので
also got your screen very cool so yeah
また、画面がとてもクールになったので
hope you've maybe gotten excited about
あなたが多分興奮していることを願っています
Raspberry Pi tonight maybe some of the
ラズベリーパイ今夜は多分いくつかの
things that we've talked about or shared
私たちが話したこと や共有したこと
is you know getting you excited about
興奮していることを知っていますか
what you can do with a Raspberry Pi and
ラズベリーパイでできること
we have not even scratched the surface
表面を 傷つけていない
not even close
程遠い
not even close there's a reason I'm
私には理由があります
surrounded in Raspberry Pi yep
ラズベリーパイに囲まれて
don't forget we've got our teespring
我々は teespringを 持っていることを忘れないでください
fundraiser going on right now you can
今行っている募金活動 あなたはできる
get a sweatshirt like I'm wearing
私が着ているような スウェットシャツ を着てください
tonight you can get t-shirts head on
今夜はTシャツを真っ先に手に入れることができます
over to cap five dot TV slash shirts and
5ドットテレビのスラッシュ シャツ にキャップをかけて
that's a great way that you can support
それはあなた が支えることが できる素晴らしい方法です
category 5 TV but also you get some swag
カテゴリ5のテレビだけでなく 、あなたはいくつかの盗品を得る
at the same time so then you're able to
同時にそれであなたはできる
Don those and show that you're a fan of
それらを着用して、あなたがのファンであることを証明してください
the show send us a picture and we will
ショーは、私たちに画像を送信して 頂きます
show it on air and we'd appreciate your
それを放送中に見せてください。
support thank you everybody thank you
応援ありがとうございました皆さん ありがとうございました
have a wonderful week yes can't believe
そう 信じることができない 素晴らしい 一週間 持って
it's time to go yeah thanks for bill
請求書を ありがとう
we'll be back next - I'll be back as
私たちは次に戻ってきます- 私は戻ってきます
well for those of you wondering she is
彼女が不思議に思っている人たちにとっても
on her honeymoon so they waited until
彼女の新婚旅行にので、彼らは まで 待っていました
until now to have the honeymoon and yes
これまでは新婚旅行をしてはい
and so they are they're traveling and
そのため、彼らは、彼らが旅行している されており 、
well it was a nice week oh yeah I'm
それはいい週でした。
jealous so
嫉妬
all right everybody have a great week
みなさん、素晴らしい一週間を
and we'll see you next time thanks to
そして私たちはあなた の 次の時間のおかげが表示されます
care
ケア
[Music]
[音楽]